, , O
least JJS O
to TO O
recession NN O
help VB O
say VBP O
. . O
millimeter NN O
of IN O
of IN O
it PRP O
. . O
, , O
Bush NNP I-per
the DT O
Swallow NNP O
of IN B-tim
Kofi NNP I-per
the DT O
spokesman NN O
Abbas NNP I-per
Pakistan NNP I-org
to TO O
as IN O
Barzani NNP B-per
calls VBZ O
was VBD O
to TO O
arrested VBD O
the DT O
of IN O
of IN O
at IN O
Essebar NNP B-org
is VBZ O
Monday NNP B-tim
and CC I-tim
a DT O
He PRP O
. . O
going VBG O
. . O
their PRP$ O
political JJ O
help NN O
in IN O
weak JJ O
and CC O
and CC O
town NN O
suspended JJ O
also RB O
president NN O
in IN O
president NN O
below IN O
, , O
, , O
as IN O
left VBD O
U.S. NNP B-geo
reportedly RB O
. . O
cases NNS O
to TO O
balloting NN O
be VB O
no DT O
after IN O
the DT O
. . O
provide VB O
sentenced VBN O
12,000 CD O
czar NN O
leader NN O
the DT O
death NN O
, , O
details NNS O
detainees NNS O
rooting VBG O
President NNP B-per
officials NNS O
for IN O
the DT O
shining VBG O
and CC O
party NN O
agreed VBD O
leaders NNS O
be VB O
. . O
Abdul NNP I-per
late JJ O
two CD O
affected JJ O
people NNS O
markets NNS O
all DT O
Party NNP I-org
Thailand NNP B-geo
to TO O
it PRP O
of IN O
television NN O
Darien NNP B-geo
Shi'ite NNP O
state NN O
civilians NNS O
in IN O
start NN O
said VBD O
will MD O
that IN O
with IN O
members NNS O
and CC O
for IN O
says VBZ O
, , O
of IN B-tim
Poland NNP B-geo
Beijing NNP B-geo
town NN O
are VBP O
theater NN O
have VBP O
and CC O
province NN O
least JJS O
by IN O
Pakistan NNP B-geo
. . O
will MD O
with IN O
to TO O
Hong NNP B-geo
by IN O
them PRP O
earlier RB O
U.S. NNP B-geo
Gadhafi NNP B-per
. . O
presidents NNS O
in IN O
Sung-ho NNP I-per
, , O
up RP O
in IN O
path NN O
ethics NNS O
and CC O
the DT O
at IN O
a DT O
table NN O
are VBP O
and CC O
of IN O
throughout IN O
say VBP O
results NNS O
, , O
during IN O
as IN O
station NN O
Heatley NNP I-per
denied VBN O
, , O
debt NN O
during IN O
in IN O
killed VBD O
body NN O
structural JJ O
. . O
he PRP O
Taliban NNP B-org
Mediterranean NNP B-geo
would MD O
the DT O
were VBD O
say VBP O
been VBN O
dictator NN O
because IN O
of IN O
Japan NNP B-geo
Blechschmidt NNP I-per
is VBZ O
one CD O
, , O
it PRP O
says VBZ O
House NNP I-org
the DT O
controversy NN O
accused VBN O
opened VBD O
achieved VBN O
angry JJ O
caters NNS O
weight NN O
for IN O
most RBS O
Vietnamese JJ B-gpe
attending VBG O
on IN O
Monday NNP B-tim
believe VBP O
of IN O
news NN O
of IN O
President NNP B-per
and CC O
the DT O
Sharon NNP I-per
calling VBG O
and CC O
through IN O
( LRB O
visiting VBG O
up RP O
been VBN O
for IN O
of IN I-tim
in IN O
said VBD O
bank NN O
Monday NNP B-tim
died VBD O
Saakashvili NNP I-per
denounced VBN O
from IN O
of IN O
Serbia NNP B-geo
Macedonia NNP B-geo
government NN O
people NNS O
say VBP O
a DT O
and CC O
's POS I-org
month NN O
, , O
Kurdish NNP B-per
captive JJ O
The DT O
the DT O
NASA NNP B-org
Revolutionary JJ B-org
Miran NNP B-geo
American JJ B-gpe
said VBD O
They PRP O
they PRP O
since IN O
but CC O
hit VBD O
planes NNS O
embassy JJ O
basic JJ O
shell NN O
's POS O
recovery NN O
been VBN O
least JJS O
is VBZ O
serious JJ O
China-North JJ O
meters NNS O
pro-independence JJ O
men NNS O
change NN O
Bush NNP I-per
to TO O
moon NN O
. . O
with IN O
Campaign NN I-org
trial NN O
prison NN O
fishermen NNS O
stalled VBN O
after IN O
. . O
, , O
Daniel NNP I-per
have VBP O
half PDT O
economy NN O
poor JJ O
finfish NN O
music NN O
leading VBG O
. . O
people NNS O
state-run JJ O
Shi'ite NNP O
. . O
continued VBN O
a DT O
least JJS O
fixings NNS O
to TO O
hospitalized VBN O
called VBD O
the DT O
. . O
opening NN O
United NNP B-org
. . O
they PRP O
currently RB O
their PRP$ O
after IN O
near IN O
al-Islam NNP I-per
leave VB O
sabotage VB O
later RB B-tim
the DT O
prowl VB O
one CD O
at IN O
been VBN O
mountain NN O
members NNS O
including VBG O
. . O
adjourned VBN O
broke VBD O
's POS O
but CC O
rebels NNS O
optimism NN O
Ossetian NNP I-geo
Rice NNP I-per
Aires NNPS I-org
controversial JJ O
News NNP I-org
ambassador NN O
option NN O
medium-term JJ O
the DT O
elections NNS O
. . O
. . O
2002 CD B-tim
bill NN O
the DT O
Spain NNP B-geo
, , O
has VBZ O
institute VB O
Saturday NNP B-tim
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
praise NN O
an DT O
Japanese JJ B-gpe
stop VB O
Anthrax NNP B-org
it PRP O
16 CD I-tim
Broad JJ B-org
. . O
Austria NNP B-org
Nesterenko NNP I-per
countries NNS O
Combs NNP B-per
with IN O
said VBD O
is VBZ O
social JJ O
points NNS O
and CC O
. . O
high JJ O
of IN O
subsequently RB O
Rights NNPS I-art
ruling NN O
with IN O
move VB O
is VBZ O
peacekeepers NNS O
President NNP B-per
reduce VB O
and CC O
assassinations NNS O
Norway NNP B-geo
after IN O
neighboring JJ O
the DT O
's POS O
police NNS O
tumors NNS O
Bashir NNP I-per
infected VBD O
died VBD O
The DT O
after IN O
when WRB O
Somalia NNP B-geo
Japanese JJ B-gpe
because IN O
severed VBD O
say VBP O
remaining VBG O
, , O
make VB O
approved VBN O
President NNP B-per
tribunal NN O
Chinese JJ B-gpe
. . O
was VBD O
already RB O
with IN O
and CC O
driving NN O
fish NN O
operation NN O
been VBN O
York NNP I-geo
havens NNS O
a DT O
the DT O
that WDT O
resume VB O
What WP O
the DT O
official NN O
there EX O
for IN O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
in IN O
mine NN O
authorities NNS O
Organization NNP I-org
fiscal JJ I-tim
of IN O
April NNP B-tim
him PRP O
Nairobi NNP B-geo
re-opened VBN O
the DT O
the DT O
in IN O
forces NNS O
the DT O
the DT O
. . O
in IN O
has VBZ O
in IN O
Congress NNP B-org
tunes NNS O
a DT O
cervical JJ O
churned VBD O
oil NN O
by IN O
incident NN O
of IN O
in IN O
. . O
, , O
World NNP B-org
than IN O
. . O
be VB O
Chongqing NNP B-org
growth NN O
diamond NN O
10 CD I-tim
people NNS O
Island NNP I-geo
, , O
met VBD O
mind NN O
militants NNS O
data NNS O
AM NNP B-art
of IN O
, , O
of IN I-geo
is VBZ O
not RB O
between IN O
debt NN O
near IN O
and CC O
15 CD I-tim
down RP O
( LRB O
. . O
compared VBN O
he PRP O
MDC NNP B-org
his PRP$ O
movements NNS O
increase VB O
from IN O
name NN O
a DT O
custody NN O
for IN O
co-founder NN O
shell NN O
( LRB O
the DT O
and CC O
to TO O
charges NNS O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
Tuesday NNP B-tim
. . O
minute NN O
former JJ O
, , O
are VBP O
" `` O
challenge NN O
insurgent JJ O
attacked VBN O
they PRP O
has VBZ O
International NNP I-org
enrichment NN O
as IN O
is VBZ O
the DT O
rebels NNS O
significant JJ O
was VBD O
Haiti NNP B-geo
of IN I-per
about IN O
number NN O
fighting NN O
session NN O
boost NN O
, , O
Bush NNP I-per
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
Africa NNP B-geo
surveys NNS O
. . O
Security NNP I-org
the DT O
staying VBG O
1,500 CD O
the DT O
Nations NNP I-org
negotiator NN O
under IN O
four CD O
of IN O
Nepal NNP B-gpe
the DT O
added VBD O
to TO O
for IN O
France NNP B-geo
parliamentary JJ O
has VBZ O
to TO O
known VBN O
Amr NNP I-per
already RB O
of IN O
terms NNS O
the DT O
aspect NN O
Burkina NNP B-per
in IN O
head NN O
to TO O
support VBP O
unemployment NN O
center NN O
Baghdad NNP B-geo
he PRP O
swam NN O
Adnan NNP B-per
resolved VBN O
June NNP B-tim
of IN I-tim
also RB O
that WDT O
five CD I-tim
Emancipation NNP I-tim
Hugo NNP I-per
say VBP O
to TO O
Iran NNP B-geo
down RP O
Turkey NNP O
records NNS O
to TO O
. . O
its PRP$ O
Obama NNP B-per
have VBP O
elections NNS O
until IN O
nuclear JJ O
southern JJ O
aggression NN O
. . O
Square NNP O
too RB O
It PRP O
Polish JJ B-gpe
Sunday NNP B-tim
nearly RB O
meeting NN O
account NN O
by IN O
. . O
headquarters NN O
the DT O
for IN O
spokesman NN O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
small JJ O
it PRP O
the DT O
. . O
by IN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
National NNP B-org
the DT O
expressed VBD O
Last JJ O
governments NNS O
through IN O
of IN O
recognize VB O
in IN O
under IN O
12 CD O
A DT O
Serbian JJ B-gpe
can MD O
's POS O
of IN O
the DT O
slight JJ O
, , O
and CC O
Marine NN I-geo
saying VBG O
measures NNS O
, , O
the DT O
, , O
Tokyo NNP B-geo
discuss VB O
nations NNS O
search NN O
soil NN O
Eastern NNP B-geo
camp NN O
. . O
Nations NNPS I-org
, , O
party NN O
. . O
pro-government JJ O
. . O
use VB O
2005 CD B-tim
The DT O
in IN O
explosion NN O
Union NNP B-org
, , O
begins VBZ O
reporters NNS O
churns VBZ O
admitted VBN O
devices NNS O
Colombian JJ B-gpe
bicycle NN O
of IN O
government NN O
a DT O
concerns NNS O
southern JJ O
before IN O
Jericho NNP B-geo
for IN O
during IN O
to TO O
. . O
are VBP O
said VBD O
Thursday NNP B-tim
surpassing VBG O
, , O
of IN O
of IN O
speech NN O
last JJ O
Ukrainian JJ B-gpe
Whoopie NNP B-per
fasten VB O
President NNP B-per
Schnyder NNP I-per
plots NNS O
of IN O
president NN O
city NN O
higher JJR O
. . O
, , O
disease NN O
Afghanistan NNP B-geo
is VBZ O
including VBG O
Ri NNP B-org
that IN O
He PRP O
among IN O
Party NN O
and CC O
includes VBZ O
an DT O
Both DT O
afternoon NN I-tim
him PRP O
against IN O
master NN O
formed VBD O
a DT O
is VBZ O
Ali NNP I-per
Friday NNP I-tim
Meanwhile RB O
army NN O
order NN O
rammed VBD O
, , O
Taliban NNP B-org
home NN O
2.5 CD O
month NN O
country NN O
nationalist NN I-org
province NN O
it PRP O
's POS O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
but CC O
the DT O
occupied VBD O
in IN O
Pinochet NNP I-per
kidnappers NNS O
land NN O
. . O
laws NNS O
that IN O
. . O
claims NNS O
Jordan NNP B-gpe
An DT O
them PRP O
. . O
has VBZ O
movie NN O
eastern JJ O
Bush NNP I-per
oil NN O
reporters NNS O
European NNP B-org
in IN O
studying VBG O
when WRB O
, , O
Bangladeshis NNS B-gpe
, , O
were VBD O
Hamas NNP B-org
is VBZ O
comment VB O
If IN O
, , O
issues NNS O
. . O
resigned VBD O
The DT O
ongoing JJ O
the DT O
the DT O
there RB O
, , O
past NN O
in IN O
expressed VBN O
Sassou-Nguesso NNP I-per
agreement NN O
a DT O
last JJ O
of IN O
Agassi NNP B-per
the DT O
the DT O
killed VBN O
. . O
At IN O
country NN O
for IN O
, , O
. . O
Kashmir NNP I-geo
local JJ O
Rafik NNP B-per
into IN O
1.5 CD O
report NN O
she PRP O
carrying VBG O
to TO O
of IN O
be VB O
about IN O
GDP NN O
in IN O
the DT O
government NN O
called VBD O
the DT O
he PRP O
still RB O
Mexico NNP B-org
confirmation NN O
's POS O
, , O
oil NN O
criticizing VBG O
100 CD O
Norte NNP B-geo
acquisition NN O
at IN O
again RB O
roadway NN O
killing VBG O
North JJ O
a DT O
80 CD O
have VB O
said VBD O
for IN O
Wardak NNP B-geo
. . O
centuries NNS O
times NNS O
Japanese JJ B-gpe
group NN O
said VBN O
holiday NN O
mine NN O
and CC O
about IN O
Nations NNPS I-org
turned VBD O
such JJ O
British JJ B-gpe
. . O
all DT O
's POS O
have VBP O
have VBP O
documents NNS O
. . O
a DT O
conflict NN O
men NNS O
God NNP B-per
some DT O
Rath NNP I-org
spoke VBD O
as IN O
. . O
are VBP O
South NNP B-geo
leave VB O
children NNS O
Osaka NNP B-geo
at IN O
to TO O
they PRP O
can MD O
information NN O
Third NNP B-per
a DT O
dry VB O
Uruzgan NNP B-geo
, , O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
continuing VBG O
July NNP B-tim
exploded VBD O
. . O
. . O
bin NNP I-per
aid NN O
part NN O
London NNP B-geo
in IN O
decline NN O
protected VBN O
development NN O
not RB O
when WRB O
said VBD O
polio NN O
of IN O
barred VBN O
's POS O
Limmt NNP B-org
torture NN O
wounded VBN O
this DT O
nations NNS O
Iraq NNP B-geo
eastern JJ O
the DT O
not RB O
secretly RB O
as IN O
Minister NNP O
released VBN O
, , O
a DT O
Roman NNP B-org
people NNS O
papers NNS O
of IN O
at IN O
have VB O
the DT O
Energy NNP I-org
Here RB O
two CD O
ease VB O
this DT O
On IN O
to TO O
traces NNS O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
been VBN O
released VBN O
to TO O
federal JJ O
put VBD O
Islamic NNP B-org
the DT O
, , O
and CC O
to TO O
Kazakhstan NNP B-per
, , O
and CC O
children NNS O
are VBP O
the DT O
Bush NNP I-per
to TO O
of IN O
, , O
in IN O
unsustainable JJ O
radio NN O
earthquake NN O
and CC O
are VBP O
also RB O
four CD O
unless IN O
boards NNS O
a DT O
Iran NNP B-geo
84-year-old JJ O
that IN O
from IN O
diplomatic JJ O
This DT O
Panama NNP B-geo
judge NN O
He PRP O
militant NN O
rate NN O
in IN O
Maliki NNP B-geo
the DT O
, , O
15 CD O
killed VBN O
told VBN O
The DT O
incident NN O
southern JJ B-geo
that IN O
win VB O
nationalities NNS O
but CC O
peace NN O
diplomatic JJ O
company NN O
Benigno NNP I-per
on IN O
warm JJ O
Tayyip NNP I-per
covers VBZ O
have VBP O
Program NNP I-org
of IN O
to TO O
economy NN O
United NNP B-geo
's POS O
up RP O
has VBZ O
because IN O
a DT O
confirmed VBN O
that WDT O
of IN O
monitoring NN O
a DT O
truck NN O
Awards NNP I-org
Foreign NNP O
Senate NNP B-org
policies NNS O
" `` O
heavily RB O
tribesmen NNS O
good JJ O
the DT O
bluegrass NN O
four CD O
with IN O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
football NN O
to TO O
say VBP O
elections NNS O
responded VBN O
ordered VBD O
condition NN O
the DT O
disaster NN O
Kurdish JJ O
that WDT O
through IN O
lower JJR O
is VBZ O
. . O
in IN O
force NN O
publicly RB O
say VBP O
plan VB O
Union NNP I-org
" `` O
and CC O
. . O
Islands NNP I-geo
in IN O
were VBD O
involving VBG O
when WRB O
philosophy NN O
protesting VBG O
wounded VBD O
Hundreds NNS O
with IN O
2003 CD B-tim
's POS I-org
East NNP B-geo
human JJ O
to TO O
schools NNS O
feeling VBG O
work NN O
terrorism NN O
, , O
In IN O
North NNP B-geo
States NNPS I-geo
Wiig NNP I-per
place NN O
needed VBD O
's POS O
American JJ B-gpe
convince VB O
and CC O
Hungary NNP B-org
sectors NNS O
have VBP O
violence NN O
threats NNS O
aircraft NN O
were VBD O
eight CD I-tim
's VBZ O
the DT O
. . O
opposition NN O
The DT B-org
Mr. NNP B-per
on IN O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
westward RB O
of IN O
traveled VBD O
diplomatic JJ O
's POS O
Mr. NNP B-per
no DT O
guides NNS O
the DT O
. . O
quoted VBN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
related VBN O
fighter NN O
for IN O
incident NN O
searching VBG O
the DT O
extremists NNS O
say VBP O
88 CD O
increase VB O
with IN O
freezing VBG O
in IN O
the DT O
government NN O
Hingis NNP I-per
The DT O
of IN O
currently RB O
could MD O
said VBD O
across IN O
League NNP I-org
incident NN O
hurled VBD O
detainees NNS O
a DT O
battling VBG O
President NNP B-per
is VBZ O
, , O
house NN O
Michael NNP B-per
is VBZ O
two CD O
In IN O
is VBZ O
several JJ O
, , O
members NNS O
But CC O
San NNP I-geo
and CC O
and CC O
30 CD O
the DT O
in IN O
of IN O
. . O
resolution NN O
nuclear JJ O
morning NN I-tim
the DT O
The DT O
in IN O
has VBZ O
of IN O
islands NNS O
harmful JJ O
Jannati NNP I-per
Ngom NNP I-per
in IN O
. . O
a DT O
retailers NNS O
despite IN O
only RB O
a DT O
's POS O
. . O
fears NNS O
the DT O
and CC O
, , O
under IN O
estate NN O
on IN O
of IN O
in IN O
chance NN O
himself PRP O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
have VBP O
Kashmir NNP O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
and CC O
U.N. NNP B-org
Obama NNP B-per
Wednesday NNP B-tim
could MD O
raising NN O
starts VBZ O
products NNS O
the DT O
their PRP$ O
. . O
Thursday NNP B-tim
enjoyed VBD O
for IN O
The DT O
the DT O
insurgents NNS O
hope VBP O
and CC O
Shyam NNP B-per
head VB O
event NN O
before IN O
Indonesian JJ B-gpe
slogans NNS O
was VBD O
evening NN I-tim
Friday NNP B-tim
whether IN O
the DT O
in IN O
down RP O
for IN O
begun VBN O
in IN O
accounts NNS O
annual JJ O
anti-terrorism JJ O
lives NNS O
to TO O
two CD O
Security NNP B-org
any DT O
into IN O
to TO O
The DT O
it PRP O
Networks NNP I-org
2008 CD B-tim
. . O
willing JJ O
city NN O
" `` O
Meanwhile RB O
with IN O
promote VB O
was VBD O
and CC O
one CD O
, , O
the DT O
. . O
sprees NNS O
, , O
it PRP O
in IN O
new JJ O
that IN O
of IN O
95,000 CD O
were VBD O
in IN O
and CC O
a DT O
facility NN O
routes NNS O
its PRP$ O
. . O
. . O
. . O
a DT O
years NNS O
's POS O
Blair NNP I-per
of IN O
the DT O
We PRP O
Gaza NNP B-geo
had VBD O
the DT O
. . O
on IN O
an DT O
Pakistan NNP B-geo
valid JJ O
up RB O
. . O
15 CD O
chronic JJ O
all PDT O
blood NN O
wage NN O
claimed VBD O
west NN O
blast NN O
for IN O
by IN O
ending VBG O
a DT O
officials NNS O
and CC O
down RB O
They PRP O
. . O
the DT O
. . O
more JJR O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
in IN O
refusing VBG O
country NN O
, , O
. . O
what WP O
from IN O
. . O
has VBZ O
its PRP$ O
capacity NN O
Mr. NNP B-per
Turkish JJ B-gpe
100 CD O
Koreans NNS B-gpe
on IN O
calling VBG O
paramilitary JJ O
camp NN O
from IN O
city NN O
new JJ O
also RB O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
drop VBP O
watched VBN O
her PRP$ O
in IN O
have VBP O
. . O
tunnel NN O
Without NNP I-org
in IN O
have VBP O
military JJ O
of IN O
it PRP O
Gulf NNP B-geo
and CC O
and CC O
hostage NN O
intended VBD O
months NNS O
people NNS O
has VBZ O
Taiwan NNP B-geo
more JJR O
against IN O
Washington NNP I-org
nuclear JJ O
governing VBG O
's POS O
his PRP$ O
of IN O
from IN O
, , O
won VBN O
the DT O
three CD I-tim
African NNP B-geo
in IN O
and CC O
administration NN O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
killing VBG O
an DT O
it PRP O
caucus NN O
2.8 CD O
include VBP O
charges NNS O
of IN O
television NN O
answered VBD O
Musharraf NNP I-per
" `` O
working-level JJ O
over IN O
airports NNS O
. . O
the DT O
Asia NNP I-geo
up RP O
district NN O
The DT O
, , O
military JJ O
who WP O
's POS O
American JJ B-gpe
globalization NN O
accord NN O
U.S.-led JJ O
Friday NNP B-tim
The DT O
employees NNS O
. . O
an DT O
, , O
Nadal NNP I-per
United NNP B-org
rainy JJ O
bill NN O
money NN O
said VBD O
telecom NN O
has VBZ O
Garrigues NNP I-per
memoir NN O
seven CD O
victim NN O
take VB O
in IN O
. . O
Department NNP O
the DT O
' POS O
U.S. NNP B-geo
focusing VBG O
fishing NN O
charges NNS O
, , O
set VBN O
Gaza NNP B-geo
to TO O
economy NN O
Nepal NNP B-gpe
and CC O
presidential JJ O
is VBZ O
interview NN O
use NN O
in IN O
Saturday NNP B-tim
resigned VBN O
process NN O
people NNS O
symbols NNS O
heavily RB O
However RB O
Egypt NNP B-geo
had VBD O
one-quarter NN O
coup NN O
a DT O
prime JJ O
Education NNP O
chariot NN O
, , O
to TO O
town NN O
troubled JJ O
said VBD O
central JJ O
Three CD O
capital NN O
's POS O
, , O
ex-boyfriend JJ O
saying VBG O
strong JJ O
former JJ O
decision NN O
new JJ O
police NN O
arid JJ O
Xinhua NNP B-org
not RB O
do VB O
his PRP$ O
the DT O
. . O
trip NN O
addressed VBD O
police NN O
and CC O
for IN O
convoy NN O
because IN O
United NNP B-org
GDP NN O
a DT O
. . O
protection NN O
government NN O
rebel NN O
allow VB O
aid NN O
of IN O
special JJ O
undermine VB O
of IN O
prison NN O
the DT O
to TO O
again RB O
suicide NN O
heels NNS O
next JJ O
. . O
spy NN O
each DT O
his PRP$ O
to IN O
On IN O
Sunday NNP B-tim
about IN O
to TO O
has VBZ O
. . O
growth NN O
, , O
do VBP O
justify VB O
that IN O
here RB O
that IN O
would MD O
During IN O
- : I-per
a DT O
reports NNS O
the DT O
as IN O
of IN O
Mohamed NNP B-geo
take VB O
cities NNS O
arrested VBN O
of IN O
Texas NNP B-geo
% NN O
being VBG O
endowed VBN O
file NN O
New NNP B-geo
is VBZ O
's POS O
oil-rich NN O
On IN O
Venezuela NNP B-geo
the DT O
Annan NNP I-per
came VBD O
the DT O
Fatah NNP B-org
as IN O
talks NNS O
charges NNS O
programs NNS O
and CC O
and CC O
, , O
Officials NNS O
. . O
died VBN O
its PRP$ O
Pyongyang NNP B-per
in IN O
by IN O
take VB O
for IN O
presidency NN O
who WP O
run-off NN O
knocking VBG O
courses NNS O
wants VBZ O
in IN O
nuclear JJ O
in IN O
sources NNS O
of IN O
More JJR O
quickly RB O
, , O
army NN O
foreign JJ O
from IN O
assist VB O
G8 NNP O
in IN O
. . O
A DT O
African JJ B-gpe
A DT O
killed VBN O
are VBP O
working VBG O
. . O
more JJR O
the DT O
the DT O
at IN O
army NN O
They PRP O
soldiers NNS O
former JJ O
will MD O
States NNPS I-geo
rock NN O
from IN O
Officials NNS O
Pakistan NNP B-gpe
Williams NNP I-org
the DT O
General NNP I-org
plans VBZ O
of IN O
transport NN O
pictures NNS O
expected VBN O
touch VB O
will MD O
comparable JJ O
most RBS O
was VBD O
with IN O
get VBP O
in IN O
fighters NNS O
even RB O
is VBZ O
defense NN O
son NN O
In IN O
western JJ O
the DT O
count NN O
show VBP O
as IN O
Cross NNP I-geo
American JJ B-gpe
On IN O
the DT O
decline NN O
that IN O
injured VBN O
that WDT O
designating VBG O
pope NN O
of IN O
, , O
will MD O
administration NN O
broken VBN O
a DT O
) RRB O
finding VBG O
that WDT O
Mongolians NNS B-gpe
Minister NNP I-per
The DT O
to TO O
hospital NN O
rebels NNS O
the DT O
, , O
warned VBD O
in IN O
point NN O
Taleban NNP B-org
police NNS O
said VBD O
The DT O
woman NN O
the DT O
including VBG O
Espirito NNP B-geo
country NN O
Mr. NNP B-per
the DT O
to TO O
Louisiana NNP B-org
is VBZ O
ability NN O
the DT O
to TO O
Moscow NNP B-geo
troops NNS O
and CC O
that WDT O
developing VBG O
the DT O
in IN O
in IN O
says VBZ O
Kofi NNP B-per
smugglers NNS O
Paralympics NNS I-org
, , O
facing VBG O
from IN O
and CC O
the DT O
. . O
aimed VBN O
processing NN O
Bank NNP B-org
held VBN O
, , O
denied VBN O
among IN O
has VBZ O
set VBN O
African NNP B-geo
contributing VBG O
clear JJ O
central JJ O
needs VBZ O
workers NNS O
admitted VBN O
% NN O
election NN O
hurricane NN O
this DT O
security NN O
's POS O
$ $ O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
operative NN O
dissolved VBN O
went VBD O
conflict NN O
oil NN O
findings NNS O
, , O
frame NN O
and CC O
called VBD O
President NNP I-per
. . O
say VBP O
hopes VBZ O
Open NNP I-eve
growth NN O
President NNP B-per
include VBP O
today NN I-tim
Iraq NNP B-geo
and CC O
troops NNS O
But CC O
a DT O
Cold NNP B-org
say VBP O
President NNP B-per
30,000 CD O
map NN O
Canadians NNS B-gpe
to TO O
the DT O
Mahmoud NNP I-per
States NNPS I-geo
the DT O
level NN O
. . O
. . O
his PRP$ O
East NNP I-geo
government NN O
third JJ O
United NNP B-org
outside IN O
. . O
been VBN O
most RBS O
be VB O
. . O
Hallandale NNP B-geo
were VBD O
with IN O
have VBP O
replaces VBZ O
studies NNS O
to TO O
and CC O
ago RB O
say VBP O
with IN O
late RB O
the DT O
to TO O
have VB O
been VBN O
the DT O
for IN O
in IN O
days NNS O
for IN O
last JJ O
immigrants NNS O
Mexico NNP I-geo
plan NN O
wounded VBN O
amid IN O
. . O
the DT O
32 CD O
Islamic NNP B-per
ended VBD O
unclear JJ O
the DT O
week NN O
stop NN O
government NN O
aid NN O
The DT O
Movement NN O
with IN O
Amnesty NNP B-org
has VBZ O
only RB O
Dr. NNP B-per
killed VBN O
Iran NNP B-geo
said VBD O
's POS O
informants NNS O
' POS O
pass VB O
it PRP O
time NN O
bombing NN O
international JJ O
reading NN O
and CC O
develop VB O
Colonel NNP O
in IN O
Iranian JJ B-gpe
Iraq NNP B-geo
war NN O
The DT B-org
dispatch VB O
. . O
world NN O
an DT O
The DT O
both DT O
said VBD O
the DT O
the DT O
this DT O
personal JJ O
of IN O
its PRP$ O
had VBD O
responsibility NN O
, , O
to TO O
( LRB O
stamp NN O
become VBP O
, , O
, , O
his PRP$ O
Mali NNP B-gpe
Clashes NNS O
settlement NN O
separatist JJ O
has VBZ O
. . O
he PRP O
of IN I-org
those DT O
other JJ O
on IN O
and CC O
. . O
line NN O
killed VBD O
discussed VBD O
million CD O
of IN O
The DT O
expected VBN O
the DT O
province NN O
to TO O
the DT O
head NN O
Hugo NNP I-per
to TO O
will MD O
withdrew VBD O
officials NNS O
the DT O
mostly RB O
construction NN O
working VBG O
says VBZ O
withdrawal NN O
approve VB O
name NN O
reconciliation NN O
in IN O
a DT O
blamed VBN O
can MD O
spokesman NN O
caused VBN O
has VBZ O
off RB O
would MD O
Musharraf NNP I-org
by IN O
a DT O
against IN O
are VBP O
ministry NN O
. . O
, , O
, , O
heir NN O
Somalia NNP B-geo
Organization NNP I-org
may MD O
a DT O
governor NN O
He PRP O
go VB O
of IN O
media NNS O
humanity NN O
Iranian JJ B-gpe
May NNP I-tim
runs NNS O
the DT O
. . O
Act NNP I-art
quickly RB O
Strip NNP I-geo
Post NNP I-org
but CC O
Commission NNP I-org
64 CD O
The DT O
U.N. NNP B-org
the DT O
receives VBZ O
down RP O
and CC O
St. NNP B-geo
The DT O
a DT O
which WDT O
caused VBD O
said VBD O
of IN O
a DT O
the DT O
this DT O
for IN O
. . O
people NNS O
of IN O
international JJ O
BEASTS NNS O
, , O
wider JJR O
been VBN O
home NN O
a DT O
killed VBN O
non-violence JJ O
a DT O
his PRP$ O
of IN O
or CC O
iron NN O
major JJ O
. . O
victory NN O
through IN O
travel VB O
from IN O
the DT O
50 CD B-tim
voluntarily RB O
military NN O
different JJ O
caused VBD O
request NN O
indefinite JJ O
's POS O
years NNS O
province NN O
Nigerian JJ B-gpe
U.N. NNP B-org
president NN O
for IN O
. . O
non-environmental JJ O
service NN O
in IN O
United NNP B-geo
killed VBN O
generals NNS O
comment NN O
a DT O
budget NN O
and CC O
currency NN O
. . O
regional JJ O
a DT O
with IN O
The DT O
Save NNP B-org
trucks NNS O
Following VBG O
killed VBN O
States NNPS I-geo
States NNPS I-geo
1945 CD B-tim
for IN O
government NN O
determine VB O
Majlis NNP O
authorities NNS O
. . O
the DT O
sugar-related JJ O
is VBZ O
concern NN O
Indonesian JJ B-gpe
this DT O
, , O
Kurdish JJ O
now RB O
rebels NNS O
I PRP O
, , O
limited VBN O
three CD O
recent JJ B-tim
groups NNS O
October NNP B-tim
security NN O
than IN O
a DT O
western JJ B-geo
cease-fire NN O
for IN O
Bush NNP I-per
warplanes NNS O
electronics NNS O
if IN O
square NN O
takeover NN O
Organization NNP O
2009 CD I-tim
beginning VBG O
is VBZ O
to TO O
alliance NN O
the DT O
to TO O
and CC O
travel NN O
Officials NNS O
say VBP O
wounded VBD O
to TO O
of IN O
traditional JJ O
not RB O
India NNP B-geo
$ $ O
at IN O
of IN O
the DT O
visit VB O
low-level JJ O
Also RB O
, , O
for IN O
attack NN O
civilians NNS O
was VBD O
's POS O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
Syria NNP B-geo
1939 CD B-tim
Western JJ B-per
. . O
in IN O
final JJ O
central JJ O
U.S. NNP B-org
has VBZ O
self-defense NN O
Virginia NNP I-geo
along RP O
their PRP$ O
out RP O
army NN O
Colombant NNP I-per
in IN O
Nepalese JJ B-gpe
opposed VBN O
of IN O
men NNS O
killed VBN O
of IN O
administrations NNS O
Kim NNP I-per
months NNS O
can MD O
only RB O
first JJ O
. . O
upcoming JJ O
Supreme NNP B-org
him PRP O
of IN O
of IN O
components NNS O
of IN O
inmates NNS O
but CC O
the DT O
should MD O
which WDT O
of IN O
Kashmir NNP I-geo
stock NN O
All DT O
World NNP O
. . O
forces NNS O
said VBD O
. . O
for IN O
Friday NNP B-tim
leaders NNS O
less JJR O
Korea NNP I-geo
hand NN O
with IN O
by IN O
to TO O
after IN O
and CC O
Britain NNP B-geo
ElBaradei NNP I-per
Konstantin NNP B-per
United NNP B-org
President NNP B-per
so-called JJ O
rubber-stamp JJ O
from IN O
East NNP I-geo
Serb JJ I-gpe
there EX O
member NN O
death NN O
However RB O
called VBD O
flag-draped JJ O
the DT O
soldiers NNS O
abuse NN O
hotels NNS O
poll NN O
met VBD O
of IN O
cut VB O
's POS O
offenses NNS O
in IN O
and CC O
elsewhere RB O
two CD O
Mosul NNP B-geo
predominantly RB O
counterattack NN O
holds VBZ O
at IN O
seats NNS O
Almost RB O
in IN O
. . O
stones NNS O
which WDT O
have VBP O
and CC O
the DT O
a DT O
Iraq NNP B-geo
been VBN O
rammed VBD O
from IN O
, , O
the DT O
China NNP B-geo
killed VBN O
as IN O
mission NN O
dismantle VB O
killing VBG O
areas NNS O
part NN O
% NN O
Iraq NNP B-org
were VBD O
mass NN O
spokesman NN O
Advisor NNP I-org
sets VBZ O
study NN O
both DT O
's POS O
. . O
's POS O
videotape NN O
such JJ O
tragedy NN O
all DT O
at IN O
for IN O
learned JJ O
freeze NN O
That DT O
African JJ B-gpe
more JJR O
an DT O
President NNP B-per
been VBN O
size NN O
blamed VBN O
, , O
without IN O
. . O
the DT O
. . O
Most JJS O
the DT O
government NN O
this DT O
Coalition NNP I-org
looted VBD O
aimed VBN O
, , O
bad JJ O
to TO O
the DT O
's POS O
U.N. NNP B-org
dereliction NN O
Mr. NNP B-per
former JJ O
fighters NNS O
than IN O
border NN O
killed VBD O
more JJR O
Wal-Mart NNP B-org
already RB O
early JJ O
to TO O
rover NN O
will MD O
the DT O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
territory NN O
been VBN O
and CC O
sector NN O
, , O
witnesses NNS O
House NNP I-org
redeploy VB O
dominion NN O
Syrian JJ B-gpe
aimed VBN O
years NNS O
Haiti NNP B-geo
to TO O
country NN O
San NNP B-geo
their PRP$ O
of IN O
were VBD O
Venezuela NNP B-geo
four CD O
the DT O
its PRP$ O
who WP O
on IN O
Baghdad NNP B-geo
talks NNS O
killed VBD O
basis NN O
as IN O
has VBZ O
Taliban NNP B-org
a DT O
Rangers NNP I-org
which WDT O
two CD O
the DT O
bunkers NNS O
before IN O
country NN O
IAEA NNP B-org
tests NNS O
voiced VBD O
Witnesses NNS O
developed VBN O
a DT O
Dozens NNS O
Iraq NNP B-geo
, , O
near-empty JJ O
the DT O
favors VBZ O
, , O
of IN O
never RB O
March NNP B-tim
have VBP O
a DT O
from IN O
years NNS O
military JJ O
Committee NNP B-org
Democratic JJ O
high-ranking JJ O
treatment NN O
. . O
of IN O
did VBD O
2001 CD B-tim
officials NNS O
A DT O
Poti NNP B-geo
The DT O
expires VBZ O
Monday NNP B-tim
island NN O
responsibility NN O
, , O
including VBG O
, , O
the DT O
internal JJ O
begun VBN O
's POS O
National NNP O
United NNP B-org
behind IN O
Geir NNP B-per
presence NN O
to TO O
last JJ O
Inflation NN O
including VBG O
was VBD O
panel NN O
An DT O
a DT O
Gulf NNP O
United NNP B-org
made VBN O
week NN O
spring NN B-tim
hijacked JJ O
each DT O
a DT O
after IN O
Catholic NNP B-geo
had VBD O
Qinghai NNP B-geo
Addis NNP B-geo
, , O
the DT O
to TO O
with IN O
end NN O
Syria NNP B-geo
to TO O
Malaysian JJ B-gpe
the DT O
the DT O
United NNP B-org
and CC O
accord NN O
to TO O
helped VBD O
1.55 CD O
a DT O
. . O
walls NNS O
in IN O
with IN O
the DT O
for IN O
South NNP B-org
tsunami NN O
suicide NN O
's POS O
whiskey NN O
, , O
its PRP$ O
was VBD O
's POS O
soldiers NNS O
to TO O
vocal JJ O
called VBN O
of IN O
surgical JJ O
the DT O
open JJ O
mired VBN O
put VBN O
days NNS O
world NN O
part NN O
in IN O
She PRP O
that IN O
monitors NNS O
grouped VBN O
and CC O
in IN O
Olympics NNPS I-geo
some DT O
the DT O
leader NN O
Eritrean JJ B-gpe
Reserve NNP I-org
late RB B-tim
of IN O
was VBD O
" `` O
the DT O
of IN O
, , O
. . O
registered VBN O
octopus NN O
and CC O
, , O
weekend NN B-tim
to TO O
Irish JJ B-gpe
of IN O
of IN O
You PRP O
the DT O
measures NNS O
conflict NN O
, , O
common JJ O
. . O
by IN O
improved VBN O
a DT O
as IN O
Robert NNP I-org
risen VBN O
minister NN O
civil JJ O
between IN O
planning VBG O
H5N1 NNP O
curb VB O
this DT O
poverty NN O
take VB O
mission NN O
1.4 CD O
Iraq NNP B-geo
and CC O
of IN O
than IN O
with IN O
Hu NNP I-per
FARC NNP B-org
company NN O
soldiers NNS O
in IN O
help VB O
working VBG O
board NN O
detained VBD O
only JJ O
117-ball JJ O
European JJ O
has VBZ O
its PRP$ O
also RB O
Sinak NNP B-geo
weather VBP O
exchange NN O
. . O
presidential JJ O
and CC O
by IN O
upon IN O
together RB O
called VBD O
hurt VB O
aggressively RB O
and CC O
foreign JJ O
the DT O
Supreme NNP I-org
sectarian JJ O
if IN O
regional JJ O
democracy NN O
. . O
Court NNP I-org
centimeter NN O
in IN O
over IN O
to TO O
with IN O
its PRP$ O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
spiked VBD O
agricultural JJ O
sent VBN O
the DT O
of IN O
more JJR O
Karzai NNP I-per
producer NN O
like IN O
newspaper NN O
with IN O
of IN O
two CD O
. . O
will MD O
. . O
areas NNS O
people NNS O
peacekeepers NNS O
debate NN O
program NN O
U.S.-led JJ O
working VBG O
Times NNP I-org
constitution NN O
. . O
Australian JJ B-gpe
last JJ O
border NN O
, , O
28 CD O
are VBP O
social JJ O
. . O
Abu NNP B-org
conditions NNS O
Tuesday NNP I-tim
series NN O
Suu NNP I-geo
a DT O
crimes NNS O
Yasser NNP B-org
State NNP B-org
women NNS O
previous JJ B-tim
United NNP B-org
the DT O
had VBD O
find VB O
insists VBZ O
stole VBP O
ways NNS O
, , O
Cabinet NNP B-geo
in IN O
41 CD O
before IN O
Bush NNP I-per
Mr. NNP B-per
agreement NN O
. . O
ordered VBD O
are VBP O
kilometers NNS O
. . O
. . O
. . O
The DT O
) RRB O
Spanish JJ B-gpe
investigating VBG O
not RB O
percent NN O
's POS O
surveillance NN O
are VBP O
Spain NNP B-geo
his PRP$ O
injured JJ O
truckers NNS O
to TO O
incentives NNS O
internal JJ O
building NN O
$ $ O
economies NNS O
boycott NN O
the DT O
See NNP I-org
the DT O
have VBP O
. . O
. . O
to TO O
down RP O
through IN O
of IN O
institutions NNS O
named VBD O
confirmed VBD O
The DT O
economic JJ O
, , O
Thursday NNP B-tim
Force NNP I-org
Swank NNP I-per
winds NNS O
to TO O
violence-ridden JJ O
year NN O
stalled VBN O
trick NN O
and CC O
reduce VB O
countries NNS O
Some DT O
is VBZ O
2003 CD B-tim
Abdel-Al NNP B-geo
, , O
Countries NNPS I-org
the DT O
government NN O
buildup NN O
six CD O
Zapatero NNP I-per
imports NNS O
warned VBN O
is VBZ O
, , O
elections NNS O
saying VBG O
scorers NNS O
presidential JJ O
as IN O
are VBP O
1994 CD I-tim
food NN O
to TO O
nation NN O
government NN O
Gaza NNP B-geo
at IN O
rains NNS O
violence NN O
of IN O
In IN O
incited VBN O
and CC O
while IN O
after IN O
History NNP I-org
Forces NNS O
and CC O
Carlos NNP I-org
increase VB O
top JJ O
also RB O
country NN O
commander NN O
for IN O
from IN O
Jewish JJ O
site NN O
eventually RB O
stopped VBD O
the DT O
and CC O
weapons NNS O
. . O
to TO O
China NNP I-org
They PRP O
person NN O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
on IN O
The DT B-org
. . O
one CD O
of IN O
majority NN O
Afghanistan NNP B-geo
Mahee NNP B-org
paramilitary JJ O
new JJ O
airport NN O
Japan NNP B-geo
always RB O
England NNP I-per
by IN O
to TO O
price NN O
Moodie NNP I-org
nationally RB O
Chad NNP B-geo
the DT O
of IN O
in IN O
chickens NNS O
stolen JJ O
separatist JJ O
, , O
UNICEF NNP B-org
he PRP O
, , O
confrontation NN O
in IN O
, , O
million CD O
Army NNP B-org
Based VBN O
fought VBN O
to TO O
central JJ O
Hindi NNP O
west NN O
, , O
Mr. NNP B-per
media NNS O
died VBD O
United NNP B-geo
Japan NNP B-geo
to TO O
proceedings NNS O
A DT O
at IN O
; ; O
for IN O
group NN O
week NN O
met VBD O
government NN O
toward IN O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
personal JJ O
fired VBN O
support NN O
, , O
what WP O
over IN O
November NNP I-tim
Slobodan NNP I-per
Witnesses NNS O
by IN O
majority NN O
authorities NNS O
constitutional JJ O
in IN O
from IN O
master NN O
a DT O
He PRP O
require VB O
in IN O
, , O
, , O
Canada NNP B-geo
Anil NNP B-org
two CD O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
recently RB O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
has VBZ O
Italy NNP B-geo
be VB O
's POS O
including VBG O
100 CD O
Kim NNP B-per
allowed VBN O
closure NN O
is VBZ O
explosion NN O
separate JJ O
Chiapolino NNP I-per
assault NN O
Katrina NNP B-tim
condolences NNS O
related VBN O
. . O
in IN O
Russian-made JJ O
flowed VBD O
July NNP B-tim
in IN O
more JJR O
The DT O
Namibia NNP B-geo
Many JJ O
conflict NN O
proposal NN O
A DT O
Algeria NNP B-geo
due JJ O
awaiting VBG O
completed VBN O
private JJ O
her PRP$ O
island NN O
1980s NNS B-tim
chief NN O
instability NN O
country NN O
that WDT O
for IN O
, , O
with IN O
in IN O
Commerce NNP B-org
explosion NN O
Atomic NNP I-org
the DT O
, , O
DNA NN O
accuse VBP O
judge NN O
other JJ O
fears NNS O
Taliban NNP B-org
troops NNS O
and CC O
court NN O
people NNS O
. . O
massive JJ O
nuclear JJ O
and CC O
an DT O
The DT O
the DT O
indicates VBZ O
comes VBZ O
on IN O
operating VBG O
by IN O
's POS O
exceptional JJ O
answers NNS O
gunmen NNS O
a DT O
Frontieres NNP B-per
2009 CD B-tim
in IN O
his PRP$ O
the DT O
called VBD O
Ahmadinejad NNP B-org
before IN O
's POS O
group NN O
for IN O
is VBZ O
armed JJ O
a DT O
chronic JJ O
with IN O
imprisoned VBN O
. . O
killed VBN O
will MD O
eastern JJ O
India NNP B-org
on IN O
a DT O
toward IN O
for IN O
say VBP O
President NNP B-per
limited JJ O
bomb NN O
is VBZ O
of IN O
in IN O
come VBP O
, , O
disrupt VB O
reality NN O
Ethiopia NNP B-geo
. . O
he PRP O
has VBZ O
rebels NNS O
five CD O
cases NNS O
States NNPS I-geo
the DT O
an DT O
the DT B-geo
web NN O
he PRP O
caregivers NNS O
instead RB O
elections NNS O
, , O
offensive NN O
's POS O
the DT O
region NN O
. . O
Emirates NNP B-org
immunized VBN O
Radical NNP I-org
newspaper NN O
suicide NN O
insurgents NNS O
Nations NNP I-org
Wen NNP B-per
the DT O
newer JJR O
recovered VBN O
30 CD I-tim
which WDT O
several JJ O
says VBZ O
Protestant NNP B-org
required VBD O
of IN O
the DT O
vote NN O
threats NNS O
. . O
China NNP B-geo
accept VB O
Bosnia-Herzegovina NNP B-geo
claiming VBG O
officials NNS O
plans VBZ O
content NN O
cooperation NN O
. . O
about IN O
supplies NNS O
30,000 CD O
one CD O
fourth NN O
of IN O
's POS O
Video NN O
the DT O
because IN O
other JJ O
say VBP O
ready JJ O
States NNPS I-geo
of IN O
to TO O
of IN O
of IN O
also RB O
Burmese JJ B-gpe
who WP O
were VBD O
reporting NN O
one-day JJ B-tim
been VBN O
is VBZ O
in IN O
has VBZ O
have VBP O
officials NNS O
routine NN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
and CC O
same-sex JJ O
pass VB O
NBC NNP B-org
prices NNS O
more JJR O
trip NN O
Fatal JJ O
also RB O
spur NN O
on IN O
Chinese-U.S. JJ O
aid NN O
a DT O
are VBP O
with IN O
Taliban NNP B-org
. . O
to TO O
Arizona NNP B-geo
Uzbek JJ B-gpe
did VBD O
Greece NNP B-geo
the DT O
security NN O
Arab NNP B-geo
of IN O
evidence NN O
suicide NN O
put VB O
hostages NNS O
is VBZ O
iftaar NNP B-eve
if IN O
policy NN O
partner NN O
North NNP B-geo
million CD O
least JJS O
would MD O
better RB O
Asian JJ O
60-thousand JJ O
fields NNS O
adult NN O
no DT O
and CC O
in IN O
were VBD O
in IN O
less JJR O
" `` O
Kashmir NNP B-geo
San NNP B-geo
allowed VBN O
Security NNP I-org
though IN O
of IN O
to TO O
purchase VB O
years NNS O
the DT O
to TO O
southern JJ O
" `` O
court NN O
Antigovernment JJ O
, , O
France NNP B-org
involve VB O
set VBN O
but CC O
two CD O
The DT B-org
elections NNS O
city NN O
Bush NNP I-per
have VBP O
presidential JJ O
in IN O
militants NNS O
kidnapped VBN O
Sunni NNP B-per
follow VBP O
Israel NNP B-geo
to TO O
Monday NNP B-tim
the DT O
to TO O
in IN O
three-judge JJ O
player NN O
National NNP B-geo
congress NN O
World NNP B-org
compound NN O
from IN O
numerous JJ O
African JJ B-gpe
possible JJ O
. . O
of IN O
Democratic NNP I-org
completely RB O
new JJ O
company NN O
; ; O
Mohammed NNP B-per
and CC O
Damascus NNP B-geo
funeral NN O
Obama NNP I-per
CNN NNP B-org
investment NN O
natural JJ O
. . O
been VBN O
, , O
the DT O
that IN O
say VBP O
by IN O
. . O
before IN O
of IN O
warning NN O
made VBN O
called VBN O
He PRP O
say VBP O
by IN O
minister NN O
moves NNS O
" `` O
of IN I-geo
pose VBP O
purposes NNS O
Condoleezza NNP B-per
the DT O
Andiwal NNP I-per
city NN O
South NNP B-geo
to TO O
new JJ O
wounded VBN O
Critics NNS O
military JJ O
and CC O
provinces NNS O
holds VBZ O
expected VBN O
Madrazo NNP I-per
also RB O
across IN O
vote NN O
Cross NNP I-org
would MD O
seemingly RB O
. . O
ministry NN O
hold VB O
reactor NN O
pled VBD O
chickens NNS O
in IN O
sent VBN O
June NNP B-tim
Thursday NNP B-tim
earlier RBR O
simulation NN O
from IN O
, , O
special JJ O
of IN O
Thai JJ B-gpe
to TO O
, , O
since IN O
Taiwan NNP B-geo
observances NNS O
government NN O
elections NNS O
center NN O
of IN O
discuss VB O
and CC O
crime NN O
next JJ O
. . O
were VBD O
continue VB O
Beijing NNP B-geo
defendants NNS O
raid NN O
captured VBN O
fails VBZ O
Spain NNP B-geo
in IN O
began VBD O
about IN O
police NNS O
of IN O
the DT O
president NN O
in IN O
to TO O
just RB O
Monday NNP B-tim
, , O
EU NNP B-org
forces NNS O
attempt NN O
packing VBG O
regularly RB O
Brazil NNP B-geo
be VB O
ease VB O
inspections NNS O
Zebari NNP I-per
from IN O
it PRP O
US NNP B-org
Interior NNP B-org
trading NN O
pressured VBN O
maneuvers NNS O
funding NN O
wrapped VBD O
two CD O
the DT O
procedure NN O
Bangladesh NNP B-geo
that IN O
$ $ O
police NNS O
basket NN O
India NNP B-geo
policy NN O
United NNP B-geo
after IN O
North NNP B-geo
construction NN O
peacekeepers NNS O
state NN O
a DT O
left VBN O
teenager NN O
North JJ B-geo
strikes NNS O
since IN O
word NN O
out IN O
to TO O
help VB O
raid NN O
study VB O
judge NN O
on IN O
, , I-tim
, , O
. . O
of IN O
Saturday NNP B-tim
of IN O
Britain NNP B-geo
In IN O
. . O
the DT O
concerns NNS O
and CC O
geographically RB O
U.S. NNP B-org
cooperation NN O
session NN O
Farouk NNP B-per
called VBD O
three CD O
since IN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
only RB O
bank NN O
are VBP O
McPherson NNP I-geo
, , O
Minister NNP O
25 CD I-tim
officials NNS O
In IN O
Economic NNP I-org
about IN O
. . O
200 CD O
. . O
. . O
the DT O
said VBD O
of IN O
Brigades NNP I-org
the DT O
Thabo NNP I-per
army NN O
let VBN O
for IN O
criticized VBD O
girls NNS O
. . O
Nepal NNP B-gpe
echo VBP O
from IN O
's POS O
are VBP O
of IN O
said VBD O
policies NNS O
know VB O
had VBD O
appears VBZ O
Friday NNP B-tim
that IN O
say VBP O
have VBP O
General NNP B-org
foreigner NN O
ban NN O
said VBN O
lives NNS O
first JJ B-tim
mingled VBN O
16 CD I-tim
making VBG O
" `` O
trade NN O
House NNP I-org
Khamenei NNP I-org
flu NN O
if IN O
Monday NNP B-tim
of IN O
. . O
a DT O
worldwide NN O
the DT O
confirmed VBN O
Venezuelan JJ B-gpe
everyday JJ O
he PRP O
birds NNS O
end NN B-tim
had VBD O
Deputy NNP B-org
Rice NNP I-per
Luiz NNP I-per
Paul NNP B-per
2005 CD B-tim
militant NN O
But CC O
Jose NNP I-per
ago RB O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
United NNP B-org
agency NN O
country NN O
more JJR O
country NN O
Mr. NNP B-per
, , O
lowering VBG O
in IN O
strong JJ O
militant NN O
. . O
. . O
police NN O
, , O
programs NNS O
people NNS O
international JJ O
quotes VBZ O
of IN I-tim
Atomic NNP I-org
expand VB O
Elsewhere RB O
for IN O
the DT O
. . O
a DT O
urging VBG O
for IN O
says VBZ O
birds NNS O
of IN O
government NN O
In IN O
visits NNS O
nation NN O
the DT O
they PRP O
it PRP O
that IN O
than IN O
manufactured VBN O
spring NN O
a DT O
more JJR O
plotter NN O
has VBZ O
say VBP O
at IN O
. . O
, , O
uprisings NNS O
instances NNS O
at IN O
while IN O
are VBP O
more JJR O
has VBZ O
police NN O
economies NNS O
say VBP O
border NN O
presenting VBG O
accompanied VBN O
and CC O
. . O
the DT O
month NN O
Jerusalem NNP B-geo
International NNP I-geo
they PRP O
Taylor NNP B-per
tourism NN O
police NN O
linked VBN O
. . O
by IN O
continent NN O
vehicle NN O
a DT O
. . O
U.S. NNP B-geo
Lohan NNP I-per
of IN O
, , O
saying VBG O
join VB O
decision NN O
say VBP O
the DT O
talks NNS O
. . O
not RB O
Fred NNP B-per
economic JJ O
of IN O
a DT O
II NNP B-eve
discussions NNS O
and CC O
group NN O
slight JJ O
U.N. NNP B-org
neighboring JJ O
% NN O
officials NNS O
the DT O
, , O
have VBP O
announced VBD O
voters NNS O
. . O
was VBD O
. . O
been VBN O
at IN O
litigation NN O
the DT O
threatens VBZ O
late JJ O
a DT O
the DT O
have VBP O
a DT O
The DT O
Namibian JJ B-gpe
that WDT O
agreed VBD O
. . O
said VBN O
telephone NN O
continue VB O
were VBD O
The DT O
part NN O
or CC O
participates VBZ O
Zealand NNP I-org
the DT O
is VBZ O
also RB O
. . O
Baghdad NNP B-geo
least JJS O
Baghdad NNP B-geo
, , O
were VBD O
also RB O
, , O
sentiment NN O
Minister NNP O
as IN O
restraint NN O
Hekmatyar NNP I-org
A DT O
. . O
two CD O
population NN O
a DT O
say VBP O
It PRP O
place NN O
now RB I-tim
mosque NN O
other JJ O
United NNP B-geo
Amin NNP I-per
Since IN B-tim
to TO O
must MD O
conduct VB O
between IN O
responsibility NN O
5.8 CD O
on IN O
votes NNS O
related VBN O
President NNP B-per
injury NN O
, , O
circumstances NNS O
was VBD O
Chief NN O
62 CD O
The DT O
Department NNP I-org
the DT O
over RP O
associates NNS O
hectare NN O
Vigorous JJ O
in IN O
The DT O
revenue NN O
island NN O
" `` O
At IN O
was VBD O
former JJ O
have VBP O
immunity NN O
an DT O
Egyptian JJ B-gpe
Korean JJ B-gpe
natural JJ O
. . O
chance NN O
. . O
Afghanistan NNP B-geo
at IN O
spread VBD O
with IN O
the DT O
December NNP I-tim
1996 CD B-tim
to TO O
insurgents NNS O
pornographic JJ O
said VBD O
. . O
a DT O
fans NNS O
insurgents NNS O
army NN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
authorities NNS O
the DT O
farm NN O
Union NNP I-org
thought VBD O
resumed VBD O
said VBD O
bird NN O
his PRP$ O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
two CD O
planned VBN O
and CC O
process NN O
plant NN O
Officials NNS O
fired VBD O
first JJ O
airport NN O
Opposition NNP O
to TO O
when WRB O
shepherd NN O
. . O
and CC O
latest JJS O
in IN O
recognize VBP O
Venezuelan JJ B-gpe
agent NN O
Africa NNP B-geo
exploded VBD O
sales NNS O
rocket NN O
fat JJ O
it PRP O
in IN I-tim
killed VBN O
troops NNS O
Abbas NNP I-per
astronauts NNS O
good JJ O
Africa NNP B-geo
newly-elected JJ O
take VB O
people NNS O
. . O
have VBP O
African NNP I-gpe
Colombia NNP B-geo
on IN O
year NN O
Guantanamo NNP B-geo
and CC O
. . O
suffocating VBG O
Madagonia NNP B-gpe
products NNS O
reach VB O
have VBP O
a DT O
suffered VBD O
former JJ O
Christians NNPS O
to TO O
, , O
But CC O
of IN O
of IN O
pilgrims NNS O
500 CD O
the DT O
reporting VBG O
ban NN O
that WDT O
which WDT O
retirees NNS O
out RP O
the DT O
, , O
to TO O
Iraq NNP B-geo
black JJ O
common JJ O
al-Qaida NNP B-org
Allert NNP I-per
southeastern JJ O
Canadian JJ B-gpe
's POS O
and CC O
not RB O
a DT O
, , O
The DT O
ultra-Orthodox JJ O
has VBZ O
keep VB O
He PRP O
China NNP B-geo
extension NN O
, , O
universal JJ O
cocaine NN O
island NN O
than IN O
and CC O
offer VB O
Shi'ite NNP B-org
, , O
with IN O
kidnappers NNS O
officials NNS O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
retreat NN O
to IN O
in IN O
out RP O
that IN O
three-quarters NNS O
plenary JJ O
who WP O
is VBZ O
caretaker NN O
Nations NNPS I-org
assuming VBG O
at IN O
30 CD O
offensive NN O
is VBZ O
in IN O
border NN O
, , O
Syria NNP B-geo
he PRP O
Thursday NNP I-tim
the DT O
Tourism NNP O
2010 CD B-tim
. . O
alliance NN O
bomb NN O
were VBD O
, , O
storm NN O
August NNP B-tim
health NN O
the DT O
in IN O
shows VBZ O
reforms NNS O
say VBP O
the DT O
a DT O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
, , O
to TO O
illegal JJ O
least JJS O
increased VBN O
the DT O
State NNP B-org
Sri NNP B-org
Islamic JJ O
Columbia NNP O
Department NNP I-org
found VBN O
to TO O
interests NNS O
% NN O
Africa NNP I-org
airspace NN O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
to TO O
of IN O
and CC O
officials NNS O
by IN O
months NNS O
drop NN O
in IN O
OAS NNP B-org
a DT O
experts NNS O
accusations NNS O
conflict NN O
and CC O
detention NN O
Israelis NNS B-gpe
tell VB O
were VBD O
. . O
again RB O
the DT O
. . O
the DT O
who WP O
has VBZ O
There EX O
in IN O
, , O
stopped VBD O
conducted VBD O
for IN O
Sharon NNP I-per
talks NNS O
Prime NNP B-per
. . O
four CD O
elected VBN O
, , O
percent NN O
release NN O
Greece NNP B-geo
a DT O
with IN O
Serb JJ I-gpe
during IN O
cleric NN O
diversify VB O
switch VB O
the DT O
channel NN O
was VBD O
parliamentary JJ O
status NN O
percent NN O
in IN O
hand-picked JJ O
Secretary-General NN O
. . O
the DT O
, , O
situation NN O
more JJR O
. . O
. . O
more JJR O
bird NN O
found VBD O
saying VBG O
have VBP O
Mr. NNP B-per
offshore JJ O
Madrid NNP I-per
payments NNS O
Chavez NNP I-per
pressure NN O
Iranian-American JJ O
of IN O
office NN O
economic JJ O
Bush NNP I-per
people NNS O
. . O
be VB O
killed VBD O
" `` O
on IN O
could MD O
his PRP$ O
islands NNS O
's POS O
to TO O
brought VBN O
Thursday NNP B-tim
write VB O
military JJ O
in IN O
, , O
areas NNS O
to TO O
. . O
outbreak NN O
as IN O
that IN O
to TO O
had VBD O
the DT O
. . O
it PRP O
cricket NN O
. . O
the DT O
Interfax NNP B-geo
children NNS O
tour NN O
a DT O
07-May CD O
also RB O
Economic NNP I-org
terrorists NNS O
resolved VBN O
some DT O
will MD O
of IN O
all DT O
conflict NN O
attacks NNS O
appointed VBD O
spark NN O
poultry JJ O
the DT O
in IN O
. . O
others NNS O
similar JJ O
killed VBN O
two CD B-tim
a DT O
hold VB O
come VBP O
than IN O
already RB O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
hefty JJ O
at IN O
recruiting NN O
question NN O
border NN O
Fire NNP B-org
agency NN O
month NN O
British JJ B-gpe
price NN O
It PRP O
latest JJS O
experienced VBD O
has VBZ O
nearly RB O
of IN O
's POS O
's POS O
last JJ O
nominal JJ O
terrorism NN O
deal NN O
chemical NN O
to TO O
says VBZ O
two CD O
and CC O
some DT O
in IN O
of IN O
's POS O
Mr. NNP B-per
in IN O
Musharraf NNP I-per
, , O
Kofi NNP B-per
, , O
guilty JJ O
capital NN O
the DT O
buildings NNS O
the DT O
military NN O
can MD O
other JJ O
reported VBN O
side NN O
the DT O
allowing VBG O
Tehran NNP B-org
early JJ O
officers NNS O
13 CD O
Mack NNP I-per
an DT O
policy NN O
Jong-Chul NNP I-per
World NNP O
a DT O
phrase NN O
killing NN O
developed JJ O
said VBD O
said VBD O
report NN O
number NN O
ashore RB O
and CC O
's POS O
and CC O
. . O
face VB O
any DT O
's POS O
from IN O
's POS O
and CC O
president NN O
's POS O
between IN O
federal JJ O
Bush NNP I-per
including VBG O
Korea NNP I-geo
to TO O
force NN O
On IN O
. . O
condition NN O
area NN O
. . O
between IN O
Bush NNP I-per
first-time JJ O
military JJ O
stationed VBD O
sue VB O
to TO O
far RB O
of IN O
's POS O
attack NN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
the DT O
to TO O
reports VBZ O
offensive NN O
the DT O
things NNS O
killed VBN O
cell NN O
in IN O
Muhammad NNP I-org
dissidents NNS O
London NNP B-geo
from IN O
speculation NN O
said VBD O
The DT O
of IN O
Friday NNP B-tim
to TO O
rains NNS O
Pakistani JJ B-gpe
Rezko NNP B-org
when WRB O
Cairo NNP B-geo
poverty-stricken JJ O
to TO O
their PRP$ O
to TO O
the DT O
. . O
has VBZ O
to TO O
City NNP I-geo
financed VBN O
2.2 CD O
, , O
If IN O
Pervez NNP I-per
troops NNS O
suspects NNS O
. . O
nuclear JJ O
will MD O
Agency NNP I-org
Tripoli NNP B-geo
Kiribati NNP B-gpe
2003 CD B-tim
disagreements NNS O
attorneys NNS O
da NNP I-per
fighting NN O
in IN O
who WP O
hookup NN O
in IN O
ground NN O
each DT O
attended VBD O
. . O
begins VBZ O
are VBP O
is VBZ O
the DT O
shut VBN O
says VBZ O
billion CD O
the DT O
encryption NN O
country NN O
mark VB O
Democratic JJ B-org
said VBD O
, , O
access NN O
police NNS O
reports NNS O
operations NNS O
the DT O
to TO O
nearly RB O
a DT O
a DT O
. . O
known VBN O
February NNP I-tim
including VBG O
embedded VBD O
It PRP O
. . O
embargo NN O
Ghazni NNP B-geo
early JJ O
close JJ O
who WP O
government NN O
militants NNS O
Council NNP I-org
it PRP O
in IN O
of IN O
Among IN O
the DT O
States NNPS I-geo
hurricanes NNS O
widespread JJ O
in IN O
people NNS O
, , O
Officials NNS O
China NNP B-geo
news NN O
. . O
's POS O
Mr. NNP B-per
U.S. NNP B-org
, , O
For IN O
Australia NNP B-geo
that IN O
of IN O
eight CD O
in IN O
in IN O
all PDT O
. . O
militants NNS O
concessions NNS O
Switzerland NNP B-geo
rebels NNS O
gunfight NN O
Brotherhood NNP B-org
and CC O
U.S. NNP B-geo
the DT O
leader NN O
strike NN O
in IN O
six CD O
monastery NN O
is VBZ O
running VBG O
has VBZ O
Congressional JJ O
has VBZ O
President NNP B-per
was VBD O
. . O
police NN O
tribunal NN O
, , O
also RB O
were VBD O
the DT O
have VBP O
under IN O
hypothetical JJ O
Canadian JJ B-gpe
explosives NNS O
Baghdad NNP B-geo
exchanged VBD O
Friday NNP B-tim
force NN O
then RB O
extremist NN O
March NNP B-tim
Internet NN O
to TO O
Johnson-Sirleaf NNP I-per
Center NNP I-org
parts NNS O
and CC O
past JJ B-tim
, , O
oil NN O
study NN O
in IN O
continuous JJ O
through IN O
it PRP O
were VBD O
in IN O
affection NN O
between IN O
must MD O
metal NN O
in IN O
. . O
Asian NNP B-org
been VBN O
Prodi NNP B-per
was VBD O
the DT O
. . O
operations NNS O
Friday NNP B-tim
several JJ O
Africa NNP I-geo
. . O
a DT O
backdrop NN O
Group NNP B-org
slower JJR O
detainees NNS O
short JJ O
may MD O
merger NN O
as IN O
on IN O
South JJ O
has VBZ O
filed VBN O
creating VBG O
official NN O
tsunami NN O
voices NNS O
at IN O
report NN O
known VBN O
early JJ O
The DT O
days NNS O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
after IN O
Britain NNP B-geo
's POS O
if IN O
preparations NNS O
the DT O
HIV-AIDS NNP O
nation NN O
Union NNP I-geo
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
quake-zone NN B-geo
. . O
and CC O
The DT O
's POS O
troops NNS O
said VBD O
culture NN O
Belgium NNP B-gpe
Sheikh NNP I-per
, , O
August NNP B-tim
in IN O
remain VBP O
fire NN O
of IN O
has VBZ O
runs NNS O
Friday NNP B-tim
famine NN O
has VBZ O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
257 CD O
, , O
the DT O
does VBZ O
said VBD O
California NNP B-geo
. . O
a DT O
says VBZ O
Iraqis NNS B-gpe
be VB O
single-party JJ O
popularity NN O
as IN O
the DT O
minutes NNS O
Indian JJ B-gpe
joining VBG O
Council NNP I-org
militancy NN O
South NNP B-geo
the DT O
to TO O
parliament NN O
fatality NN O
Christmas NNP B-tim
exodus NN O
says VBZ O
fate NN O
province NN O
the DT O
. . O
. . O
For IN O
's POS O
's POS O
at IN O
U.N. NNP B-org
The DT O
guns NNS O
Minister NNP I-per
U.S. NNP B-geo
has VBZ O
. . O
7 CD O
he PRP O
Prosecutors NNS O
terrorists NNS O
the DT O
Benin NNP B-geo
mining NN O
chase NN O
extradition NN O
. . O
U.N. NNP B-org
1.5 CD O
and CC O
the DT O
left VBN O
. . O
released VBN O
says VBZ O
Israeli NN B-gpe
, , O
summit NN O
's POS O
of IN O
February NNP B-tim
killed VBN O
new JJ O
how WRB O
country NN O
the DT O
fight NN O
asked VBN O
the DT O
ethnicity NN O
Bashar NNP I-per
U.S. NNP B-geo
affairs NNS O
manufacturing NN O
people NNS O
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
media NNS O
avian JJ O
because IN O
an DT O
, , O
pre-launch JJ O
the DT O
the DT O
. . O
of IN O
refiners NNS O
lack NN O
peso NN O
say VBP O
G-8 NNP B-org
Laden NNP I-per
region NN O
According VBG O
The DT O
Sri NNP B-org
permission NN O
a DT O
Canadian JJ B-gpe
immediate JJ O
ONE CD O
since IN O
activity NN O
which WDT O
should MD O
's POS O
Bolton NNP I-per
fourth JJ O
week NN O
these DT O
in IN O
258 CD O
Greenpeace NNP B-geo
as IN O
urging VBG O
for IN O
Britain NNP B-geo
include VB O
that IN O
about IN O
logging VBG O
62 CD B-tim
EU NNP B-org
, , O
against IN O
not RB O
. . O
poor JJ O
documents NNS O
reported VBN O
September NNP B-tim
wife NN O
that IN O
restore VB O
innocent JJ O
said VBD O
has VBZ O
reaching VBG O
1947 CD B-tim
the DT O
anywhere RB O
clothes NNS O
banks NNS O
Al-Sadr NNP B-per
including VBG O
. . O
from IN O
say VBP O
in IN O
at IN O
two CD I-tim
well RB O
outside IN O
says VBZ O
will MD O
Sunday NNP B-tim
block VB O
mother NN O
in IN O
profits NNS O
, , O
cut VBN O
that WDT O
as IN O
during IN O
is VBZ O
in IN O
in IN O
. . O
and CC O
than IN O
industry NN O
to TO O
Ghimire NNP I-org
deeply RB O
his PRP$ O
160 CD O
defense NN O
possibility NN O
families NNS O
government NN O
week NN O
Vienna NNP O
both DT O
for IN O
were VBD O
helicopter NN O
. . O
packed VBN O
. . O
to TO O
. . O
. . O
the DT O
. . O
to TO O
goods NNS O
's POS O
, , O
. . O
crimes NNS O
, , O
March NNP B-tim
honor NN O
Austria NNP B-geo
Russian JJ B-gpe
chorus NN O
taking VBG O
half NN I-tim
intelligence NN O
. . O
robotic JJ O
it PRP O
business NN O
Industrial NNP I-geo
the DT O
Jerusalem NNP B-geo
and CC O
conclude VB O
people NNS O
hospital NN O
. . O
at IN O
Hurricane NNP O
up RP O
were VBD O
more JJR O
terrorist JJ O
people NNS O
in IN O
a DT O
, , O
Zone NNP B-geo
. . O
six CD O
In IN O
the DT O
at IN O
to TO O
Horne NNP I-per
, , O
building NN O
in IN O
. . O
The DT O
and CC O
made VBD O
an DT O
the DT O
what WP O
environmental JJ O
handled VBN O
Mullah NNP B-org
not RB O
Venezuela NNP B-geo
found VBN O
five CD O
Mosque NN I-tim
that IN O
the DT O
of IN O
is VBZ O
officers NNS O
thousands NNS O
government NN O
region NN O
nuclear JJ O
endorsed VBD O
Canadian JJ B-gpe
of IN O
Shi'ite NNP O
is VBZ O
immigrants NNS O
not RB O
October NNP B-tim
, , O
to TO O
defeated VBN O
his PRP$ O
, , O
rates NNS O
, , O
last JJ O
contracted VBD O
months NNS O
Vincennes NNP I-org
years NNS O
About RB O
of IN O
is VBZ O
a DT O
Military JJ O
telling VBG O
fierce JJ O
and CC O
an DT O
aid VB O
River NNP I-geo
first JJ O
with IN O
50 CD O
world NN O
West NNP B-geo
policy NN O
tackle VB O
components NNS O
aviaries NNS O
Lebanon NNP B-geo
four CD O
Eve NNP I-geo
between IN O
of IN O
will MD O
Though IN O
Muslims NNS I-org
a DT O
killing VBG O
but CC O
inauguration NN O
the DT O
. . O
largest JJS O
simple JJ O
continue VB O
in IN O
private JJ O
the DT O
before IN O
along IN O
. . O
news NN O
of IN O
Energy NNP I-org
suspects VBZ O
observers NNS O
bombers NNS O
Africa NNP I-geo
to TO O
already RB O
about IN O
arsenic NN O
videotaped VBN O
10 CD I-tim
of IN O
deal VB O
, , O
the DT O
as IN O
silver NN O
to TO O
refugee NN O
the DT O
nearby JJ O
in IN O
's POS O
investigation NN O
battling VBG O
fatal JJ O
has VBZ O
they PRP O
posted VBD O
to TO O
hospital NN O
Togo NNP B-gpe
's POS O
rebel NN O
, , O
if IN O
in IN O
shareholders NNS O
those DT O
Moscow NNP B-org
peace NN O
World NNP O
said VBD O
improve VB O
medications NNS O
foreign JJ O
system NN O
is VBZ O
. . O
who WP O
. . O
attend VB O
cancel VB O
a DT O
new JJ O
an DT O
has VBZ O
. . O
. . O
in IN O
faces VBZ O
some DT O
to TO O
away RB O
the DT O
al-Qaida NNP B-org
all DT O
. . O
the DT O
killed VBD O
say VBP O
to TO O
million CD O
Delhi NNP I-geo
being VBG O
is VBZ O
interests NNS O
Analysts NNS O
up RP O
to TO O
previously RB O
groups NNS O
billion CD O
as IN O
mounting VBG O
poll NN O
tycoon NN O
bars NNS O
neighbors NNS O
, , O
to TO O
's POS O
afternoon NN I-tim
investment NN O
suspected JJ O
ministers NNS O
the DT O
refers VBZ O
Arnold NNP I-org
stabilize VB O
the DT O
birds NNS O
huge JJ O
engagement NN O
from IN O
civilians NNS O
police NN O
human JJ O
coalition NN O
ties NNS O
. . O
answer VB O
's POS O
" `` O
recruits NNS O
Superhighway NNP I-org
Group NNP B-org
Turkish JJ B-gpe
so RB O
crimes NNS O
the DT O
about IN O
a DT O
approved VBD O
weeks NNS O
defeat NN O
Chad NNP B-geo
Haiti NNP B-tim
" `` O
treating VBG O
's POS O
" `` O
rifle NN O
trials NNS O
including VBG O
's POS O
a DT O
and CC O
manufacturing NN O
of IN O
blocking VBG O
you PRP O
others NNS O
a DT O
percent NN O
. . O
countries NNS O
South JJ B-org
Wednesday NNP B-tim
Mei NNP B-per
The DT O
Details NNS O
The DT O
near IN O
officers NNS O
Vahidi NNP I-per
weapons NNS O
, , O
western JJ B-geo
been VBN O
the DT O
found VBD O
in IN O
percent NN O
country NN O
recent JJ O
Taliban NNP B-org
, , O
, , O
Iles NNP B-geo
month NN O
Several JJ O
. . O
York NNP I-org
were VBD O
tissue NN O
defendant NN O
Aye NNP I-per
Land NNP O
Sea NNP I-geo
as IN O
did VBD O
. . O
military JJ O
U.S. NNP B-geo
proved VBN O
Police NNS O
Moqtada NNP B-per
were VBD O
2003 CD B-tim
and CC O
since IN O
Washington NNP B-geo
in IN O
gasoline NN O
of IN I-org
says VBZ O
Zimbabwe NNP B-org
drivers NNS O
Tunisians NNPS I-org
Brigadier NNP B-org
people NNS O
what WP O
attacks NNS O
say VBP O
rare JJ O
hours NNS O
a DT O
least JJS O
Justice NNP B-org
agreements NNS O
some DT O
and CC O
another DT O
in IN O
in IN O
Minister NNP B-per
to TO O
outbreak NN O
that WDT O
others NNS O
the DT O
from IN O
The DT O
to TO O
this DT O
said VBD O
out RP O
said VBD O
lot NN O
known VBN O
suspected JJ O
the DT O
interim JJ O
neigh NN O
15 CD O
of IN O
been VBN O
said VBN O
2001 CD B-tim
and CC O
Four NNP B-art
structural JJ O
place NN O
about IN O
McGrady NNP I-per
were VBD O
origin NN O
tents NNS O
sharply RB O
the DT O
to TO O
, , O
two CD B-tim
the DT O
upon IN O
seen VBN O
the DT O
Gazprom NNP B-geo
plant NN O
Shi'ite NNP B-org
an DT O
an DT O
they PRP O
of IN O
said VBD O
the DT O
parliamentary JJ O
of IN O
the DT O
for IN O
the DT O
years NNS O
3,700 CD O
However RB O
in IN O
international JJ O
would MD O
Monday NNP B-tim
from IN O
remarks NNS O
joint JJ O
, , O
series NN O
and CC O
and CC O
are VBP O
result NN O
has VBZ O
in IN O
thousands NNS O
In IN O
Chad NNP B-geo
. . O
were VBD O
rockets NNS O
told VBD O
main JJ O
was VBD O
Hungary NNP B-org
first JJ O
, , O
Kabungulu NNP I-org
scores NNS O
they PRP O
overseeing VBG O
tidal JJ O
killed VBN O
that WDT O
procession NN O
man NN O
Europrean JJ O
had VBD O
investor NN O
Zealand NNP I-geo
the DT O
said VBD O
, , O
killed VBN O
oil NN O
has VBZ O
security NN O
group NN O
in IN O
man NN O
Liaoning VBG O
have VBP O
areas NNS O
saying VBG O
say VB O
an DT O
the DT O
were VBD O
and CC O
. . O
of IN O
the DT O
for IN O
Europe NNP B-geo
holds VBZ O
amortization NN O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
health NN O
that WDT O
Comprehensive NNP B-org
Marlon NNP B-per
military JJ O
with IN O
of IN O
Robert NNP I-per
say VBP O
of IN O
discussing VBG O
least JJS O
after IN O
. . O
the DT O
fees NNS O
nuclear JJ O
Ituri NNP B-geo
murders NNS O
theorized VBN O
, , O
in IN O
on IN O
health NN O
he PRP O
since IN B-tim
said VBD O
leave VB O
been VBN O
unemployment NN O
Peshawar NNP B-geo
Fiorina NNP I-per
past NN O
reform VB O
Georgia NNP B-geo
's POS O
Venezuelan JJ B-gpe
speech NN O
its PRP$ O
a DT O
before IN O
of IN O
Herald NNP B-per
the DT O
meeting NN O
Foreign NNP B-org
Washington NNP B-geo
separate JJ O
bodies NNS O
President NNP B-per
of IN O
rebel-held JJ O
progressive JJ O
offered VBD O
that IN O
. . O
from IN O
money NN O
with IN O
Musharraf NNP I-per
who WP O
East NNP I-geo
10 CD B-tim
national JJ O
nation NN O
. . O
, , O
taxation NN O
are VBP O
saw VBD O
others NNS O
moving VBG O
that IN O
, , O
the DT O
not RB O
called VBN O
airport NN I-geo
. . O
Central NNP I-org
government NN O
high JJ O
the DT O
The DT O
Gazprom NNP B-per
also RB O
tensions NNS O
against IN O
than IN O
's POS O
Cross NNP I-geo
no DT O
Pakistani JJ B-gpe
say VBP O
be VB O
recently RB O
superiors NNS O
Somali JJ B-gpe
British JJ B-gpe
the DT O
point NN O
Shabab-held JJ O
in IN O
Janeiro NNP I-geo
killings NNS O
a DT O
treaty NN O
another DT O
Democratic NNP I-org
complaints NNS O
Aristide NNP I-per
2005 CD B-tim
critics NNS O
the DT O
says VBZ O
Rangoon NNP B-org
. . O
British JJ B-gpe
insurgents NNS O
and CC I-org
and CC O
The DT O
Abu NNP B-org
they PRP O
the DT O
that DT O
with IN O
President NNP I-per
Olmert NNP I-per
from IN O
millions NNS O
news NN O
after IN O
which WDT O
prison NN O
" `` O
. . O
isolation NN O
Saturday NNP B-tim
October NNP B-tim
that WDT O
upon IN O
people NNS O
in IN O
the DT O
under IN O
the DT O
" `` O
the DT O
have VB O
) RRB O
the DT O
supporters NNS O
is VBZ O
week NN O
northern JJ O
apparent JJ O
are VBP O
the DT O
armored JJ O
Thursday NNP B-tim
four CD O
is VBZ O
group NN O
. . O
respective JJ O
first RB O
Moscow NNP B-geo
York NNP I-org
al-Qaida NNP B-org
a DT O
Widely RB O
. . O
The DT O
seven CD O
communities NNS O
and CC O
flow NN O
parties NNS O
were VBD O
died VBN O
farms NNS O
broke VBD O
that IN O
by IN O
is VBZ O
key JJ O
-- : O
3 CD I-tim
a DT O
Assembly NNP I-org
suffered VBN O
London NNP B-geo
deterioration NN O
It PRP O
said VBD O
solid JJ O
Khabarovsk NNP B-geo
arrested VBD O
, , O
world NN O
Joye NNP B-per
a DT O
stole VBD O
pay VB O
ousted VBD O
India NNP B-geo
Thanks NNS O
to TO O
bomb VB O
remain VBP O
said VBD O
in IN O
a DT O
provides VBZ O
in IN O
challenges NNS O
uranium NN O
tearful JJ O
the DT O
to TO O
by IN O
Separately RB O
in IN O
empty JJ O
They PRP O
, , O
has VBZ O
also RB O
Iran NNP B-geo
Attorney-General JJ O
it PRP O
consulate NN O
years NNS O
forced VBN O
Abbas NNP I-per
were VBD O
agent NN O
aggravating VBG O
than IN O
. . O
say VBP O
to TO O
face VB O
Iran NNP B-geo
tractor NN O
remain VB O
in IN O
Putin NNP I-per
Lebanon NNP B-geo
there EX O
. . O
The DT O
his PRP$ O
patrol NN O
plane NN O
kind NN O
also RB O
Basque JJ O
strains NNS O
in IN O
the DT O
issue NN O
Human NNP I-org
say VBP O
. . O
. . O
that IN O
" `` O
15 CD O
the DT O
rocket NN O
quit VB O
urgent JJ O
has VBZ O
and CC O
. . O
deposits NNS O
power NN O
the DT O
. . O
for IN O
the DT O
military JJ O
Hamas NNP B-org
leading VBG O
in IN O
Hill NNP I-per
state NN O
seashore NN O
a DT O
in IN O
the DT O
runs NNS O
were VBD O
were VBD O
of IN O
then RB O
. . O
landmark NN O
who WP O
give VB O
of IN O
missiles NNS O
won VBD O
of IN O
Taliban NNP B-org
Friday NNP B-tim
he PRP O
. . O
no DT O
forces NNS O
off RP O
, , O
extremist NN O
were VBD O
and CC O
Labor NNP B-org
. . O
. . O
Waziristan NNP I-geo
meet VB O
, , O
organizations NNS O
al-Arian NNP B-geo
Mauritania NNP B-geo
province NN O
elections NNS O
the DT O
, , O
the DT O
remaining VBG O
Russian JJ B-gpe
forces NNS O
the DT O
causes NNS O
launched VBD O
take VBP O
- : I-tim
continues VBZ O
to TO O
Friday NNP B-tim
has VBZ O
cutting VBG O
major JJ O
- : O
was VBD O
refused VBD O
day NN O
Several JJ O
to TO O
that IN O
138 CD B-tim
U.N. NNP B-geo
when WRB O
at IN O
Strip NNP I-geo
to TO O
November NNP B-tim
nuclear JJ O
Askar NNP I-per
credit-driven JJ O
storm NN O
people NNS O
the DT O
ideas NNS O
people NNS O
Chad NNP B-geo
Sino-Tibetan JJ O
be VB O
( LRB O
Balkenende NNP I-per
the DT O
The DT O
, , O
Zebari NNP B-per
contain VB O
, , O
Washington NNP B-geo
Friday NNP B-tim
days NNS O
new JJ O
says VBZ O
forecasters NNS O
Bush NNP I-per
shots NNS O
the DT O
the DT O
said VBD O
in IN O
for IN O
50 CD O
of IN O
and CC O
1921 CD I-tim
post NN O
the DT O
threat NN O
successful JJ O
U.S. NNP B-geo
killed VBN O
killed VBN O
Because IN O
PKK NNP B-org
minister NN O
EU NNP B-org
. . O
has VBZ O
of IN O
Islamist JJ O
crew NN O
people NNS O
as RB O
to TO O
elections NNS O
and CC O
A DT O
orchestrating VBG O
, , O
difficult JJ O
. . O
another DT O
riding VBG O
They PRP O
rule NN O
with IN O
is VBZ O
man NN O
leaders NNS O
. . O
nothing DT O
landmark NN O
21-year-old JJ O
nuclear JJ O
constitution NN O
ally NN O
. . O
further JJ O
security NN O
Justices NNS O
proposal NN O
ranked VBD O
interim JJ O
history NN O
precaution NN O
includes VBZ O
Israel NNP B-geo
court NN O
was VBD O
ensure VB O
increased VBN O
Viktor NNP B-per
no DT O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
Bole NNP O
also RB O
problems NNS O
are VBP O
, , O
two CD O
Strip NNP I-org
over IN O
payments NNS O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
used VBN O
. . O
Democratia NNP I-per
would MD O
's POS O
officials NNS O
the DT O
President NNP B-per
said VBN O
Ashura NNP B-geo
this DT O
threatened JJ O
were VBD O
. . O
again RB O
village NN O
to TO O
oil NN O
official NN O
address VB O
of IN O
northeastern JJ O
asked VBD O
Sonia NNP B-per
dangerous JJ O
the DT O
Iran NNP B-geo
the DT O
broadened VBN O
terrorist JJ O
will MD O
such JJ O
Tutsis NN B-org
forces NNS O
of IN O
hospitalized VBN O
a DT O
and CC O
, , O
on IN O
at IN O
Mr. NNP B-per
of IN O
. . O
verdict NN O
. . O
saying VBG O
Afghanistan NNP B-geo
the DT O
's POS O
is VBZ O
substantially RB O
The DT O
and CC O
for IN O
Hamas NNP B-org
Secret NNP B-org
mature JJ O
members NNS O
in IN O
province NN O
easily RB O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
than IN O
because IN O
Iraq NNP B-geo
in IN O
poultry NN O
Secretary-General NNP I-geo
compassion NN O
voted VBN O
submitting VBG O
will MD O
. . O
brings VBZ O
powers NNS O
He PRP O
several JJ O
agencies NNS O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
unharmed JJ O
troops NNS O
the DT O
bomber NN O
year NN O
from IN O
, , O
fencing VBG O
has VBZ O
Somalia NNP B-geo
. . O
destroyed VBD O
March NNP B-tim
. . O
The DT O
' POS O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
, , O
to TO O
Fatah NNP B-geo
said VBD O
along IN O
driving VBG O
, , I-tim
oil NN O
al-Qaida NNP B-org
attack NN O
of IN O
Witnesses NNS O
began VBD O
tens NNS O
forest NN O
originally RB O
shortly RB O
the DT O
its PRP$ O
groups NNS O
Thursday NNP B-tim
06-Mar CD O
the DT O
Some DT O
. . O
of IN O
an DT O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
. . O
. . O
since IN O
new JJ O
world NN O
and CC O
argument NN O
border NN O
War NNP O
officials NNS O
often RB O
revenues NNS O
safety NN O
or CC O
. . O
security NN O
agency NN O
lost VBD O
A DT O
west JJ O
with IN O
donors NNS O
killed VBN O
it PRP O
to TO O
in IN O
northeastern JJ O
since IN B-tim
names NNS O
, , O
in IN O
diplomatic JJ O
and CC O
for IN O
train NN O
services NNS O
in IN O
reduction NN O
attacks NNS O
. . O
the DT O
As IN O
money NN O
accusing VBG O
officers NNS O
company NN O
to TO O
has VBZ O
one CD O
in IN O
bus NN O
deputy NN O
Eastern NNP B-geo
in IN O
humanitarian JJ O
left VBN O
known VBN O
safety NN O
. . O
the DT O
from IN O
late JJ O
-- : O
. . O
31 CD O
take VB O
The DT O
say VBP O
for IN O
shot VBN O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
there EX O
. . O
the DT O
foundations NNS O
the DT O
towns NNS O
it PRP O
There EX O
captain NN O
, , O
in IN O
sidelines NNS O
announced VBD O
the DT O
Merapi NNP I-geo
commented VBN O
benefits NNS O
Westminster NNP B-org
's POS I-org
Pakistan NNP B-geo
or CC O
views VBZ O
to TO O
1,500 CD O
the DT O
American JJ B-gpe
collapsed VBD O
's POS O
the DT O
she PRP O
the DT O
attacker NN O
Monday NNP B-tim
Bush NNP I-per
triggered VBD O
killing VBG O
the DT O
its PRP$ O
barricade NN O
and CC O
The DT O
for IN O
with IN O
, , O
neighboring VBG O
a DT O
's POS O
abducted JJ O
said VBD O
. . O
has VBZ O
Egypt-Gaza NNP O
Uzbekistan NNP B-org
New NNP B-geo
The DT O
responsibility NN O
the DT O
anyone DT O
governments NNS O
war NN O
the DT O
riots NNS O
's POS O
now RB O
earthquake-ravaged JJ B-tim
process NN O
finances NNS O
main JJ O
age NN O
with IN O
at IN O
gifts NNS O
, , O
Top NNP B-per
capital NN O
agreement NN O
former JJ O
Ass NNP O
Cheney NNP B-per
government NN O
House NNP I-org
results NNS O
hopes VBZ O
Mr. NNP B-per
, , O
violence NN O
troops NNS O
address NN O
said VBD O
of IN O
say VBP O
to TO O
measures NNS O
to TO O
, , O
companies NNS O
state NN O
forces NNS O
arrests NNS O
deeper JJR O
, , O
Iraqi JJ B-org
constitutional JJ O
the DT O
. . O
200 CD O
to TO O
independence NN O
, , O
Staff NNP I-org
he PRP O
Pyongyang NNP B-geo
, , O
by IN O
writings NNS O
's POS O
threatened VBN O
groups NNS O
carried VBD O
night NN I-tim
- IN I-tim
city NN O
. . O
fraud NN O
and CC O
The DT B-org
spokesman NN O
to TO O
was VBD O
is VBZ O
, , O
as RB O
had VBD O
tribes NNS O
a DT O
price NN O
flu NN I-nat
Tokyo NNP B-geo
Bashar NNP I-per
to TO O
firing VBG O
suicide NN O
a DT O
by IN O
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
from IN O
object VBP O
, , O
seven CD O
more RBR O
First NNP I-org
U.S.-based JJ O
deputy NN O
economies NNS O
of IN O
Saturday NNP B-tim
over IN O
directly RB O
fears NNS O
significant JJ O
U.S. NNP B-geo
Colombia NNP B-geo
country NN O
suspects NNS O
businessman NN O
newspaper NN O
oil-rich JJ O
to TO O
hit VBD O
bag NN O
on IN O
a DT O
drinking VBG O
the DT O
Abdul NNP B-per
agreement NN O
has VBZ O
country NN O
, , O
about IN O
the DT O
assured VBD O
reported VBD O
finding VBG O
massive JJ O
straight JJ I-tim
Prime NNP B-per
Prime NNP I-per
of IN O
his PRP$ O
" `` O
authorities NNS O
meeting NN O
prosecution NN O
PAD NNP O
only JJ O
with IN O
to TO O
police NN O
1979 CD B-tim
cut VBD O
week-long JJ B-tim
General NNP B-per
in IN O
, , O
the DT O
. . O
The DT O
runoff NN O
Institute NNP I-org
) RRB O
last JJ O
. . O
also RB O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
diplomat NN O
a DT O
institutions NNS O
three CD O
, , O
world NN O
build VB O
Norway NNP B-geo
transparency NN O
strategic JJ O
in IN O
this DT O
Iran NNP B-geo
numbers NNS O
Morales NNP B-per
's POS O
Minister NNP I-per
U.S. NNP B-geo
Lebanese JJ B-gpe
than IN O
Darfur NNP B-geo
with IN O
UTC NNP I-tim
also RB O
Arabia NNP I-geo
found VBN O
than IN O
says VBZ O
. . O
Clashes NNS O
read VBN O
- : O
's POS O
in IN O
, , O
suicide NN O
drive NN O
of IN O
surrounding VBG O
capture NN O
Monday NNP B-tim
dialogue NN O
the DT O
said VBD O
" `` O
attacks NNS O
at IN O
is VBZ O
's POS O
operating VBG O
some DT O
I PRP O
its PRP$ O
in IN O
Thursday NNP B-tim
's POS O
to TO O
the DT O
at IN O
's POS O
Hakimi NNP B-geo
previously RB O
North NNP B-gpe
" `` O
of IN O
and CC O
a DT O
have VBP O
was VBD O
of IN O
several JJ O
. . O
Atomic NNP I-org
that IN O
the DT O
Liberation NNP I-org
blamed VBN O
could MD O
the DT O
of IN O
put VBD O
claws NNS O
Poverty NN B-org
Major NNP B-per
peacefully RB O
earnings NNS O
they PRP O
. . O
over IN O
insurgent NN O
. . O
the DT O
border NN O
academy NN O
border NN O
bomber NN O
greeted VBD O
Saturday NNP B-tim
tourism NN O
Republican-led JJ O
she PRP O
nuclear JJ O
board NN O
women NNS O
Houston NNP B-geo
Foreign JJ O
The DT O
The DT O
Union NNP I-org
for IN O
. . O
. . O
. . O
, , O
The DT O
pedestrians NNS O
of IN O
's VBZ O
killed VBD O
Rwanda NNP B-geo
demand VB O
the DT O
security NN O
. . O
long JJ O
in IN O
at IN O
has VBZ O
U.S. NNP B-geo
after IN O
prison NN O
favor NN O
, , O
the DT O
Iranian JJ B-gpe
the DT O
heels NNS O
proclaimed VBD O
Emomali NNP I-per
resolved VBN O
, , O
remained VBN O
in IN O
later RB O
after IN O
banners NNS O
is VBZ O
several JJ O
of IN O
the DT O
Security NNP I-org
with IN O
violence NN O
bad JJ O
firefight NN O
a DT O
nations NNS O
found VBN O
in IN O
out RP O
and CC O
. . O
year NN O
The DT O
Islamist NNP O
On IN O
has VBZ O
Suu NNP I-geo
Zimmermann NNP I-per
I PRP O
car NN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
Admiral NNP O
year NN O
and CC O
lunar NN O
killed VBD O
ward NN O
are VBP O
in IN O
down RB O
are VBP O
torrential JJ O
group NN O
forces NNS O
a DT O
Taleban NNP B-org
into IN O
officials NNS O
says VBZ O
is VBZ O
offensive NN O
Syria NNP B-geo
remain VBP O
a DT O
further RBR O
insurgent JJ O
Peschke NNP I-per
of IN O
on IN O
in IN O
intervention NN O
the DT O
filed VBD O
want VB O
a DT O
to TO O
Ophelia NNP B-per
's POS O
attack NN O
the DT O
blast NN O
of IN O
their PRP$ O
crew NN O
" `` O
war NN O
. . O
. . O
Fidel NNP B-per
reassured VBD O
than IN O
for IN O
exploded VBD O
. . O
culmination NN O
, , O
of IN O
group NN O
- : I-tim
Zvornik NNP B-geo
this DT O
African JJ B-gpe
U.S. NNP B-geo
the DT O
200 CD O
and CC O
al-Aqsa NNP B-org
and CC O
US NNP B-geo
and CC O
fair JJ O
but CC O
of IN O
human JJ O
prevented VBN O
was VBD O
in IN O
common JJ O
Musab NNP I-org
positioning NN O
by IN O
U.N. NNP B-org
ethical JJ O
have VBP O
said VBD O
the DT O
being VBG O
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
savings NNS O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
to TO O
GDP NN O
, , O
a DT O
Delhi NNP I-geo
week NN O
of IN O
infrastructure NN O
to TO O
. . O
almost RB O
families NNS O
% NN O
of IN O
the DT O
dispute NN O
police NN O
island NN O
lower JJR O
in IN O
appearing VBG O
that IN O
they PRP O
leaders NNS O
Ethiopia NNP B-geo
, , O
could MD O
approval NN O
Mr. NNP B-per
of IN O
UN-negotiated JJ O
Japanese JJ B-gpe
with IN O
such JJ O
oil NN O
next JJ O
Bulgaria NNP B-geo
. . O
capital NN O
infected VBN O
, , O
set VBN O
assists NNS O
holiday NN O
production NN O
financial JJ O
world NN O
the DT O
are VBP O
when WRB O
the DT O
month NN O
nation NN O
2000 CD B-tim
fighting VBG O
army NN O
is VBZ O
. . O
expected VBN O
" `` O
Doetinchem NNP B-geo
port NN O
if IN O
comments NNS O
, , O
and CC O
with IN O
. . O
Indian-controlled JJ B-geo
after IN O
to TO O
7,000 CD O
Lahoud NNP I-per
majority NN O
in IN O
says VBZ O
in IN O
would MD O
to TO O
Cleveland NNP B-geo
The DT O
China NNP B-geo
all DT O
measure NN O
indoor JJ O
fiscal JJ O
moved VBD O
laundering NN O
January NNP B-tim
Security NN O
on IN O
Organization NNP I-org
groups NNS O
, , O
. . O
, , O
where WRB O
last JJ O
ABC NNP B-org
new JJ O
boat NN O
. . O
killed VBD O
and CC O
independence NN O
, , O
Bogota NNP B-org
they PRP O
saying VBG O
The DT O
against IN O
Israel NNP B-geo
hydropower NN O
. . O
have VBP O
million CD O
dignitaries NNS O
to TO O
in IN O
grandson NN O
calm JJ O
of IN O
send VB O
Taleban NNP B-org
would MD O
of IN O
. . O
the DT O
and CC O
Sunday NNP B-tim
is VBZ O
heavy JJ O
will MD O
virus NN O
support NN O
Minister NNP B-per
after IN O
tour NN O
China NNP B-geo
has VBZ O
unity NN O
extremist NN O
advertisements NNS O
some DT O
incursion NN O
to TO O
with IN O
region NN O
kilometers NNS O
next JJ O
between IN O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
provocation NN O
of IN O
a DT O
contend VBP O
bombings NNS O
the DT O
. . O
long JJ O
Sunday NNP B-tim
new JJ O
has VBZ O
in IN O
six CD B-tim
headed VBN O
would MD O
African JJ B-gpe
Bush NNP I-per
years NNS O
West NNP B-geo
U.S. NNP B-org
the DT O
for IN O
war NN O
the DT O
crude JJ O
violence NN O
The DT B-org
wounding VBG O
, , O
between IN O
debris NN O
of IN O
. . O
bus NN O
raids NNS O
. . O
formally RB O
Desmond NNP I-org
Council NNP I-org
Kalmykia NNP B-geo
the DT O
and CC O
land NN O
Security NNP I-org
least JJS O
Western JJ O
U.S. NNP B-org
visit VB O
party NN O
event NN O
the DT O
blasts NNS O
allies NNS O
, , O
the DT O
shops NNS O
group NN O
ruling NN O
not RB O
parts NNS O
attacks NNS O
and CC O
, , O
United NNP B-geo
supplier NN O
of IN O
Hutu NNP B-org
passing VBG O
not RB O
the DT O
of IN O
is VBZ O
beyond IN O
a DT O
it PRP O
. . O
American NNP O
. . O
next JJ O
as IN O
said VBD O
rebels NNS O
against IN O
, , O
says VBZ O
protesters NNS O
a DT O
Surgeon NNP B-per
illegally RB O
homes NNS O
Libby NNP I-per
document NN O
August NNP B-tim
died VBN O
government NN O
to TO O
Also RB O
And CC O
the DT O
, , O
was VBD O
it PRP O
the DT O
ripping VBG O
morning NN I-tim
Iraq NNP B-geo
a DT O
parties NNS O
disappearance NN O
the DT O
Amazon NNP I-tim
known VBN O
weak JJ O
dynamic JJ O
cross-border JJ O
in IN O
by IN O
to TO O
greater JJR O
taxi NN O
singles NN O
the DT O
previously RB O
Lanka NNP I-gpe
drafting VBG O
the DT O
demanded VBN O
Putin NNP I-per
Mr. NNP B-per
to TO O
mass NN O
. . O
in IN O
no DT O
was VBD O
, , O
most JJS O
celebrating VBG O
to TO O
forces NNS O
has VBZ O
Wall NNP I-org
resulting VBG O
target NN O
. . O
. . O
saying VBG O
held VBN O
expects VBZ O
Sunday NNP B-tim
died VBN O
a DT O
abductors NNS O
conflict NN O
to TO O
bombs NNS O
so IN O
at IN O
's POS O
over IN O
has VBZ O
United NNP B-org
Sunday NNP B-tim
Simba NNP I-org
children NNS O
war NN O
, , O
's POS O
rebel JJ O
, , O
take VB O
the DT O
are VBP O
Sadr NNP B-geo
anniversary NN I-tim
. . O
over RP O
be VB O
million CD O
impact NN O
95 CD O
to TO O
rebels NNS O
deft NN O
when WRB O
' POS O
separate JJ O
planning NN O
Militant JJ O
forces NNS O
and CC O
rest NN O
is VBZ O
the DT O
in IN O
U.S. NNP B-gpe
elections NNS O
on IN O
it PRP O
power NN O
speeches NNS O
P. NNP B-per
tally NN O
between IN O
the DT O
crew NN O
the DT O
Friday NNP B-tim
U.S.-led JJ O
a DT O
indicates VBZ O
was VBD O
independents NNS O
said VBD O
. . O
passenger NN O
effort NN O
six-year JJ B-tim
with IN O
officials NNS O
program NN O
's POS O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
interim JJ O
preconditions NNS O
aboard RB O
in IN O
of IN O
barred VBN O
Madrid NNP B-geo
in IN O
the DT O
obtain VB O
western JJ O
and CC O
life NN O
war NN O
inmate NN O
people NNS O
in IN O
government NN O
to TO O
claims NNS O
President NNP B-per
need VB O
improvements NNS O
small JJ O
Police NNS O
the DT O
and CC O
a DT O
Mr. NNP B-per
's POS O
impediment NN O
as IN O
critics NNS O
the DT O
rings NNS O
back RB O
, , O
where WRB O
, , O
violence NN O
the DT O
Ocean NNP I-geo
already RB O
Ottoman NNP B-org
alert NN O
Motion NNP B-org
the DT O
the DT O
President NNP B-per
clear JJ O
district NN O
on IN O
Mr. NNP B-per
were VBD O
to TO O
highly RB O
However RB O
west NN O
Kazakhstan NNP B-geo
the DT O
spreading VBG O
by IN O
city NN O
State NNP I-org
injured VBN O
within IN B-tim
some DT O
opposition NN O
Jose NNP I-per
arrested VBN O
China NNP B-geo
crimes NNS O
Near NNP B-geo
killed VBN O
it PRP O
has VBZ O
. . O
opposition NN O
" `` O
. . O
round NN O
who WP O
and CC O
The DT O
needed VBN O
three CD O
parliamentary JJ O
heavily RB O
two CD O
early JJ O
to TO O
places NNS O
to TO O
for IN O
the DT O
Commission NNP I-org
have VBP O
mishandled VBN O
" `` O
journalists NNS O
on IN O
Prospects NNS O
Governor NNP I-per
what WP O
lull NN O
the DT O
said VBD O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
the DT O
contractor NN O
hit VBN O
official NN O
unacceptable JJ O
Insurgents NNS O
another DT O
the DT O
expansion NN O
end VB O
decision NN O
in IN O
depends VBZ O
Mohammed NNP B-geo
nuclear JJ O
new JJ O
than IN O
of IN O
United NNP B-geo
launched VBD O
CH-47 NNP B-org
the DT O
over IN O
process NN O
to TO O
bulldozers NNS O
and CC O
Bashar NNP I-per
Kurdish JJ O
and CC O
sabotage NN O
of IN O
for IN O
of IN O
enhancing VBG O
week NN O
Afghanistan NNP B-geo
the DT O
honor VB O
been VBN O
in IN O
U.S. NNP B-org
at IN O
during IN O
a DT O
Ivory NNP B-org
negotiations NNS O
. . O
, , O
Authority NNP O
. . O
says VBZ O
the DT O
now RB O
who WP O
. . O
Arbitration NNP I-org
has VBZ O
it PRP O
to TO O
their PRP$ O
caused VBD O
to IN O
Rumsfeld NNP I-per
for IN O
Daily NNP B-org
Pakistan NNP B-geo
the DT O
. . O
, , O
combined VBN O
promise NN O
Zevallos NNP I-per
, , O
ethnic JJ O
. . O
, , O
a DT O
southern JJ B-geo
to TO O
A DT O
. . O
the DT O
AN DT O
as IN O
The DT O
not RB O
the DT O
Australian JJ B-gpe
been VBN O
Karzai NNP I-per
a DT O
a DT O
said VBD O
beginning VBG O
UK NNP B-org
figure NN O
if IN O
peace NN O
him PRP O
the DT O
were VBD O
vote NN I-tim
percent NN O
Another DT O
Yomiuri NNP B-geo
Egyptian JJ B-gpe
in IN O
Colombia NNP B-geo
must MD O
Pakistani JJ B-gpe
Horn NNP I-tim
at IN O
Al-Fayfi NNP O
during IN O
short NN O
Abu NNP B-per
50 CD O
camp NN O
attacks NNS O
water NN O
see VB O
. . O
the DT O
's POS I-org
, , O
leader NN O
consumers NNS O
reported VBD O
not RB O
of IN I-org
did VBD O
new JJ O
growth NN O
team NN O
and CC O
Democracy NNP I-org
competitiveness NN O
has VBZ O
. . O
, , O
they PRP O
immediately RB O
Nigeria NNP B-geo
Mr. NNP B-per
. . O
The DT O
Office NNP I-org
waiting VBG O
's POS B-tim
rise VB O
, , O
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
alternative JJ O
aimed VBN O
planet NN O
, , O
. . O
criticized VBN O
was VBD O
were VBD O
the DT O
greenhouse NN O
, , O
canceled VBD O
appears VBZ O
agreed VBD O
be VB O
died VBN O
The DT O
the DT O
. . O
the DT O
was VBD O
and CC O
the DT O
The DT O
The DT O
encouraging JJ O
it PRP O
Airbus NNP B-art
. . O
of IN O
Maori NNP O
Thailand NNP B-geo
for IN O
demonstrations NNS O
rate NN O
has VBZ O
accepting VBG O
Congo NNP I-geo
and CC I-org
Karachi NNP B-geo
has VBZ O
uranium NN O
week NN O
a DT O
Soviet JJ O
the DT O
thousands NNS O
. . O
has VBZ O
say VBP O
Fathi NNP B-per
the DT O
across IN O
Mr. NNP B-per
three CD O
President NNP B-per
for IN O
into IN O
a DT O
militant JJ O
critic NN O
poultry NN O
massacre NN O
that IN O
. . O
Home NNP B-org
forces NNS O
hunger NN O
for IN O
are VBP O
have VBP O
first RB O
two CD O
Sunnis NNS O
boosted VBD O
. . O
on IN O
blast NN O
on IN O
the DT O
billion CD O
says VBZ O
9 CD I-tim
in IN O
about IN O
organizations NNS O
of IN O
only RB O
says VBZ O
slow JJ O
of IN O
songs NNS O
1 CD O
of IN O
amid IN O
the DT O
in IN O
using VBG O
Russian JJ B-gpe
claimed VBN O
in IN O
rights NNS O
hoping VBG O
patrol NN O
behind IN O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
leadership NN O
Taiwan NNP B-geo
depicting VBG O
climate NN O
has VBZ O
that IN O
United NNP B-geo
the DT O
Foreign NNP B-org
ministry NN O
been VBN O
U.N.-African NNP B-org
. . O
the DT O
attacks NNS O
32,000 CD O
it PRP O
force NN O
from IN O
in IN O
Sunday NNP B-tim
he PRP O
twice RB O
have VBP O
Service NNP I-org
At IN O
, , O
majority NN O
in IN O
a DT O
representatives NNS O
country NN O
to TO O
operative JJ O
to TO O
for IN O
sovereignty NN O
met VBD O
four CD O
The DT O
a DT O
's POS O
her PRP$ O
chemical NN O
. . O
was VBD O
say VBP O
Minister NNP I-per
extremely RB O
reporters NNS O
province NN O
. . O
world NN O
of IN O
with IN O
than IN O
with IN O
questioned VBN O
Tom NNP I-per
to TO O
Bighi NNP I-per
, , O
, , O
this DT O
elected VBN O
and CC O
Betar NNP B-org
have VBP O
out RP O
British JJ B-gpe
Latortue NNP I-per
three CD B-tim
must MD O
deadliest JJS O
in IN O
people NNS O
new JJ O
achieve VB O
the DT O
made VBN O
year NN O
. . O
unions NNS O
Treatment NNP B-org
girl NN O
Baquba NNP B-geo
Bureau NNP I-org
to TO O
must MD O
U.N. NNP B-geo
and CC O
compared VBN O
power NN O
allotment NN O
's POS O
a DT O
the DT O
gave VBD O
for IN O
occurred VBD O
private JJ O
Uzbek JJ B-gpe
for IN O
contentious JJ O
in IN O
two CD O
Afghans NNS B-gpe
five CD B-tim
would MD O
to TO O
's POS O
already RB O
Nouri NNP B-per
. . O
Office NNP I-org
Party NNP I-org
tabloid NN O
won VBN O
the DT O
incident NN O
began VBD O
than IN O
But CC O
Monday NNP B-tim
state NN O
exploded VBD O
deployed VBN O
week NN O
who WP O
and CC O
they PRP O
confidence NN O
have VBP O
Authorities NNS O
" `` O
market-oriented JJ O
made VBD O
National NNP B-geo
ownership NN O
the DT O
officials NNS O
most RBS O
new JJ O
their PRP$ O
in IN O
of IN O
with IN O
suspicion NN O
and CC O
Petra NNP O
new JJ O
weather NN O
travel VB O
of IN O
to TO O
or CC O
Beijing NNP B-geo
has VBZ O
daily NN O
hideouts NNS O
Nepal NNP B-gpe
foreign JJ O
could MD O
Khartoum NNP B-org
and CC O
giant NN O
widely RB O
to TO O
remain VB O
a DT O
people NNS O
siege NN O
that WDT O
also RB O
- IN O
of IN O
's POS O
militias NNS O
Sirte NNP B-geo
were VBD O
being VBG O
a DT O
several JJ O
, , O
Mr. NNP B-per
in IN O
is VBZ O
the DT O
institute NN O
last JJ O
divided VBN O
contributing VBG O
. . O
Tuesday NNP B-tim
The DT O
officials NNS O
head NN O
a DT O
homes NNS O
Colombo NNP B-geo
government NN O
an DT O
Afghanistan NNP B-geo
Abbas NNP I-per
, , O
Mr. NNP B-per
was VBD O
Christians NNS O
between IN O
ethnic JJ O
after IN O
Halutz NNP I-per
military JJ O
over IN O
a DT O
, , O
1996 CD B-tim
Cypriot JJ I-gpe
Jordan NNP B-gpe
, , O
and CC O
either DT O
Polish JJ B-gpe
been VBN O
convoys NNS O
release NN O
Officials NNS O
violence NN O
attacked VBN O
. . O
figures NNS O
their PRP$ O
western JJ O
Blair NNP I-per
The DT O
supporting VBG O
ten JJ O
decided VBD O
ensured VBD O
hostage NN O
posted VBD O
seizure NN O
said VBD O
Forecasters NNS O
. . O
of IN O
to TO O
November NNP B-tim
" `` O
officers NNS O
personnel NNS O
won VBD O
provided VBN O
attack NN O
upward RB O
became VBD O
of IN O
did VBD O
was VBD O
in IN O
producing VBG O
unified JJ O
apologized VBN O
absolute JJ O
the DT O
. . O
, , O
killed VBN O
soil NN O
attack NN O
's POS O
country NN O
the DT O
War NNP O
United NNP B-geo
. . O
, , O
allowed VBN O
have VBP O
( LRB O
. . O
the DT O
willing JJ O
. . O
he PRP O
people NNS O
been VBN O
on IN O
, , O
that IN O
NATO-led JJ O
Reporters NNP B-org
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
to TO O
has VBZ O
two CD O
Morocco NNP B-org
this DT O
Iraq NNP B-geo
. . O
care NN O
say VBP O
the DT O
city NN O
demonstrators NNS O
China NNP B-org
projects NNS O
swaths NNS O
The DT O
Chad NNP B-geo
hamburgers NNS O
Herat NNP B-geo
to TO O
vote NN O
is VBZ O
seen VBN O
signed VBN O
for IN O
includes VBZ O
. . O
capital NN O
security NN O
President NNP B-per
season NN O
1975 CD B-tim
been VBN O
investigation NN O
one CD O
a DT O
minister NN O
the DT O
, , O
van NN O
statement NN O
other JJ O
at IN O
Scottish JJ B-gpe
, , O
General NNP B-org
than IN O
be VB O
Halutz NNP I-per
to TO O
aid NN O
. . O
appeared VBD O
opposition NN O
United NNP B-geo
of IN O
humanitarian JJ O
in IN O
. . O
astronauts NNS O
the DT O
, , O
subsidiary NN O
national JJ O
mark VB O
eventually RB O
at IN O
were VBD O
by IN O
the DT O
Enforcement NNP I-org
economic JJ O
50.9 CD O
process NN O
1980s NNS B-tim
Fraenzi NNP B-per
Islam NNP B-geo
province NN O
members NNS O
chief NN O
are VBP O
. . O
and CC O
$ $ O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
. . O
Regents NNPS I-org
, , O
. . O
would MD O
cold JJ O
of IN O
planning VBG O
United NNP B-geo
Middle NNP B-geo
flew VBD O
mourning NN O
year NN O
assassination NN O
the DT O
team NN O
. . O
of IN O
year NN O
a DT O
Teodoro NNP B-org
ignored VBN O
giants NNS O
in IN O
Kirkuk NNP I-org
Five CD O
Israeli-Palestinian JJ O
raided VBD O
have VBP O
for IN O
media NNS O
in IN O
has VBZ O
entry NN O
travel NN O
Anti-Corruption NNP B-org
on IN O
have VBP O
crew NN O
the DT O
a DT O
sheet NN O
astronauts NNS O
with IN O
, , O
as IN O
the DT O
of IN O
to TO O
violence NN O
civilians NNS O
, , O
Caracas NNP B-geo
officer NN O
involving VBG O
others NNS O
general NN O
of IN O
the DT O
contain VB O
the DT O
Mr. NNP B-per
of IN O
world NN O
of IN O
. . O
was VBD O
to TO O
said VBD O
. . O
ago RB O
remains VBZ O
to TO O
factory NN O
a DT O
there EX O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
slaves NNS O
Palestinian JJ B-gpe
law NN O
in IN O
his PRP$ O
killed VBN O
has VBZ O
living VBG O
that IN O
the DT O
West NNP B-org
% NN O
MDC NNP B-org
, , O
backed VBN O
. . O
nothing DT O
in IN O
an DT O
of IN O
U.S. NNP B-org
the DT O
entering VBG O
The DT O
from IN O
operation NN O
to TO O
WHO NNP B-org
Korea NNP I-geo
rates NNS O
. . O
de NNP I-geo
the DT O
to TO O
powers NNS O
. . O
sets NNS O
Sergeant NNP B-per
who WP O
the DT O
since IN O
. . O
attacks NNS O
$ $ O
during IN O
authorities NNS O
The DT O
The DT O
South NNP B-geo
government NN O
on IN O
or CC O
, , O
saying VBG O
Mr. NNP B-per
coalition NN O
Islands NNP I-geo
that WDT O
Hamid NNP I-per
about IN O
by IN O
West NNP B-org
% NN O
stressed VBD O
the DT O
two CD O
Malta NNP B-geo
, , O
Sergei NNP B-org
the DT O
is VBZ O
others NNS O
a DT O
Jackson NNP B-per
States NNPS I-geo
, , O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
Monday NNP B-tim
minister NN O
bodies NNS O
in IN O
its PRP$ O
away RB O
to TO O
becomes VBZ O
to TO O
Mottaki NNP I-per
the DT O
Forces NNPS I-org
worries VBZ O
. . O
the DT O
West JJ O
plan NN O
With IN O
has VBZ O
, , O
on IN O
Committee NNP I-org
his PRP$ O
abductions NNS O
5,00,000 CD O
is VBZ O
the DT O
Abbas NNP I-per
to TO O
its PRP$ O
into IN O
. . O
where WRB O
the DT O
the DT O
of IN O
from IN O
Voice NNP O
, , O
authorities NNS O
, , O
on IN O
separate JJ O
Saddam NNP B-per
nationwide JJ O
and CC I-tim
deal NN O
a DT O
quit VBD O
States NNPS I-geo
at IN O
Hussein NNP I-per
Turkey NNP B-geo
David NNP B-per
whole JJ B-tim
The DT O
all DT O
recent JJ B-tim
2008 CD O
a DT O
bird NN O
have VBP O
a DT O
surrounded VBN O
troops NNS O
ruling NN O
all DT O
spiritual JJ O
fire NN O
Differences NNS O
gathered VBN O
Kosachev NNP I-per
States NNPS I-geo
. . O
decision NN O
A DT O
the DT O
by IN O
a DT O
The DT O
seven CD O
. . O
Orleans NNP I-geo
facilities NNS O
of IN O
, , O
exploration NN O
part NN O
through IN O
However RB O
in IN O
he PRP O
Korea NNP I-geo
President NNP B-per
median NN O
in IN O
investment NN O
Afghan JJ B-gpe
appealed VBD O
. . O
at IN O
to TO O
report NN O
only RB O
control NN O
Annan NNP I-per
Muslim NNP B-org
being VBG O
for IN O
billion CD O
and CC O
and CC O
once RB O
% NN O
people NNS O
Damadola NNP B-geo
and CC O
reservists NNS O
In IN O
state NN O
. . O
to TO O
" `` O
August NNP B-tim
in IN O
States NNPS I-org
made VBD O
of IN O
crisis NN O
coalition NN O
percent NN O
, , O
John NNP B-per
deteriorate VBP O
security NN O
of IN O
, , O
and CC O
quitting NN O
privatization NN O
it PRP O
president NN O
agree VB O
gunmen NNS O
infected VBN O
rights NNS O
few JJ B-tim
say VBP O
Mogadishu NNP B-geo
Spears NNPS B-per
month NN O
electronically RB O
IMF NNP B-org
major JJ O
the DT O
statement NN O
. . O
to TO O
says VBZ O
the DT O
Somalia NNP B-geo
reliance NN O
. . O
a DT O
agencies NNS O
Two CD O
good JJ O
government NN O
. . O
waving VBG O
Children NNP O
, , O
in IN O
attack NN O
in IN O
presidential JJ O
Ass NNP O
for IN O
winter NN O
investors NNS O
of IN O
crime NN O
targets NNS O
conference NN O
German JJ B-gpe
the DT O
. . O
junta NN O
increases NNS O
The DT O
pledge NN O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
lawsuit NN O
match NN O
involving VBG O
Van NNP I-per
infected VBN O
Russia NNP B-geo
production NN O
of IN O
order NN O
included VBD O
that IN O
Spanish JJ B-gpe
named VBD O
and CC O
for IN O
NASA NNP B-org
for IN O
in IN O
for IN O
programs NNS O
bird VBN O
physical JJ O
resolution NN O
He PRP O
an DT O
officials NNS O
made VBN O
vacuum NN O
. . O
to TO O
. . O
by IN O
Ramadan NNP I-tim
chest NN O
indicates VBZ O
between IN O
independence NN O
bomb VB O
intention NN O
Chavez NNP I-per
down RP O
said VBD O
Zardari NNP O
released VBN O
's POS O
explosives NNS O
high JJ O
acted VBD O
a DT O
Officials NNS O
a DT O
approved VBN O
evening NN I-tim
of IN O
he PRP O
kidnap VBP O
city NN O
his PRP$ O
The DT O
have VBP O
Zabul NNP B-geo
but CC O
Hungarian NNP B-org
not RB O
. . O
bomb NN O
that IN O
new JJ O
in IN O
) RRB O
Russia NNP B-geo
centrifuge NN O
" `` O
Daoud NNP I-org
the DT O
fraud NN O
's POS O
criticizing VBG O
a DT O
Venezuela NNP B-geo
American JJ B-gpe
The DT O
takeover NN O
trademark NN O
developments NNS O
round NN O
now RB O
NATO NNP B-org
They PRP O
Bowlers NNS O
, , O
is VBZ O
breakaway JJ O
protest NN O
Poverty NN O
the DT O
companies NNS O
materials NNS O
of IN O
group NN O
eight-tenths NNS O
the DT O
other JJ O
Asia NNP B-geo
to TO O
's POS O
the DT O
are VBP O
horseback NN O
the DT O
suspend VB O
added VBD O
Mr. NNP B-per
say VBP O
forces NNS O
North NNP B-geo
order NN O
Wednesday NNP B-tim
Caracas NNP B-geo
al-Fahd NNP I-per
Venezuela NNP B-geo
Turkish JJ B-gpe
30 CD O
signifies VBZ O
, , O
role NN O
Najaf NNP B-geo
to TO O
. . O
Hassan NNP B-per
burst VBP O
phosphates NNS O
the DT O
year NN O
of IN O
stations NNS O
to TO O
government NN O
until IN O
He PRP O
sworn VBN O
. . O
2001 CD B-tim
Affairs NNP I-org
was VBD O
Finance NNP O
interfering VBG O
to TO O
, , O
takes VBZ O
teacher NN O
Warsaw NNP B-org
problems NNS O
of IN O
. . O
down RP O
honest JJ O
hurricanes NNS O
newspaper NN O
but CC O
Senegal NNP B-geo
States NNPS I-geo
total NN O
, , O
oil NN O
. . O
week NN O
late JJ O
China NNP B-geo
fare VB O
and CC O
infiltration NN O
three CD O
said VBD O
plane NN O
is VBZ O
fire NN O
was VBD O
least JJS O
outside IN O
condition NN O
manufactured JJ O
March NNP I-tim
Intelligence NNP O
Island NNP I-geo
instructions NNS O
logistical JJ O
clash NN O
weeks NNS O
Assembly NNP O
. . O
Research NNP I-org
new JJ O
settlements NNS O
economy NN O
of IN O
Tehran NNP B-geo
on IN O
been VBN O
doctor NN O
's POS O
direct JJ O
attend VB O
loss NN O
to TO O
Although IN O
British JJ B-gpe
of IN O
. . O
deaths NNS O
the DT O
bird NN O
say VB O
. . O
. . O
a DT O
Authorities NNS O
insurgents NNS O
of IN O
Somalia NNP B-geo
of IN O
Pakistani JJ B-gpe
also RB O
the DT O
was VBD O
meeting VBG O
officials NNS O
told VBD O
government NN O
targets NNS O
of IN O
bring VB O
a DT O
another DT O
. . O
check VB O
's POS O
Hwang NNP I-per
expenses NNS O
plane NN O
last JJ O
on IN O
a DT O
threatens VBZ O
Minister NNP I-per
of IN O
month NN O
of IN O
killed VBN O
's POS O
there EX O
remain VBP O
Fox NN O
U.S. NNP B-geo
consular NN O
landed VBD O
Prime NNP B-per
to TO O
- : I-tim
up RP O
now RB O
European JJ O
their PRP$ O
a DT O
unimaginable JJ O
's POS O
power NN O
of IN O
planning VBG O
no DT O
in IN O
control NN O
war NN O
cooperate VB O
Thursday NNP B-tim
May NNP B-tim
The DT O
Prime NNP B-per
, , O
Morris NNP I-per
in IN O
Jakarta NNP B-geo
will MD O
bodies NNS O
in IN O
program NN O
is VBZ O
approved VBN O
after IN O
leaders NNS O
. . O
areas NNS O
's POS O
against IN O
credible JJ O
she PRP O
Cyprus NNP B-org
opened VBN O
. . O
, , O
six CD O
have VBP O
North NNP B-geo
the DT O
from IN O
army NN O
immigration NN O
flu NN O
effective JJ O
at IN O
repercussions NNS O
community NN O
there EX O
Peace NNP I-org
of IN O
, , O
in IN O
Iran NNP B-geo
Mr. NNP B-per
to TO O
World NNP B-org
says VBZ O
the DT O
Netherlands NNP I-geo
as IN O
to TO O
36 CD O
and CC O
Sunday NNP B-tim
and CC O
Titan NNP B-geo
over IN O
. . O
more JJR O
tennis NN O
but CC O
practice VB O
at IN O
12 CD O
The DT O
for IN O
rock NN O
put VBN O
. . O
between IN O
next JJ O
gain NN O
alike RB O
Yoon-jeong NNP I-geo
Revolutionary NNP B-eve
meeting VBG O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
in IN O
Somalia NNP B-geo
communities NNS O
that IN O
life NN O
would MD O
. . O
between IN O
Anderson NNP B-geo
; ; O
The DT O
breakup NN O
suffering NN O
including VBG O
enrichment NN O
States NNPS I-geo
since IN O
single-party JJ O
choices NNS O
cleared VBD O
of IN O
Rights NNP I-org
Mr. NNP B-per
discounts NNS O
Times NNP I-org
Critics NNS O
, , O
to TO O
down RP O
. . O
to TO O
scenarios NNS O
has VBZ O
did VBD O
corporate JJ O
with IN O
French JJ B-gpe
Chadian JJ B-gpe
Yoon-jeong NNP I-per
Marinin NNP I-per
a DT O
a DT O
and CC O
. . O
it PRP O
told VBD O
falls VBZ O
to TO O
Panyu NNP B-geo
on IN O
of IN O
participation NN O
mid-1990s NNS I-geo
all-time JJ O
are VBP O
has VBZ O
help VB O
poisoned VBN O
what WP O
four CD O
United NNP B-geo
freed VBN O
were VBD O
, , O
Police NNS O
basketball NN O
freed VBN O
destabilizing VBG O
, , O
St. NNP B-geo
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
a DT O
's POS O
near IN O
bid NN O
who WP O
Administration NNP O
Venezuela NNP B-geo
on IN O
's POS O
The DT O
crisis NN O
system NN O
U.S. NNP B-gpe
by IN O
coalition NN O
to TO O
does VBZ O
York NNP I-geo
the DT O
a DT O
Ramadan NNP B-eve
terror NN O
jet NN O
particular JJ O
climbed VBD O
, , O
again RB O
Indian JJ B-gpe
have VBP O
The DT O
system NN O
policies NNS O
a DT O
rebels NNS O
and CC O
soldier NN O
emergency NN O
conflict NN O
the DT O
committed VBN O
percent NN O
state NN O
as IN O
urged VBN O
surgery NN O
calling VBG O
for IN O
no DT O
be VB O
. . O
the DT O
Association NNP I-org
proceedings NNS O
to TO O
. . O
three CD O
to TO O
but CC O
held VBN O
by IN O
Major NNP B-org
for IN O
Bank NNP I-org
meters NNS O
is VBZ O
killed VBN O
giving VBG O
20 CD O
hunters NNS O
home-grown JJ O
, , O
Sergeant NNP I-per
list NN O
the DT O
a DT O
in IN O
was VBD O
the DT O
of IN O
some DT O
follow VB O
has VBZ O
in IN O
the DT O
Islam NNP B-geo
Harcourt NNP B-per
China NNP B-geo
few JJ I-tim
, , O
of IN O
the DT O
last JJ O
Greek JJ B-gpe
Darfur NNP B-geo
the DT O
Mr. NNP B-per
of IN O
York NNP I-org
that IN O
late JJ O
city NN O
can MD O
and CC O
At IN O
market NN O
's POS O
this DT O
die VBP O
crowds NNS O
destruction NN O
party NN O
after IN O
while IN O
the DT O
Department NNP I-org
of IN O
of IN O
investigation NN O
The DT O
in IN O
was VBD O
. . O
separate JJ O
, , O
Bilfinger NNP B-org
's POS O
the DT O
Mr. NNP B-per
day NN O
. . O
the DT O
first JJ O
constraints NNS O
a DT O
instead RB O
2007 CD B-tim
the DT O
himself PRP O
first JJ O
in IN O
, , O
's POS O
security NN O
deep JJ O
load NN O
other JJ O
release NN O
from IN O
by IN O
closely RB O
seven CD O
as IN O
, , O
of IN O
were VBD O
, , O
" `` O
He PRP O
estimate NN O
but CC O
light NN O
the DT O
put VBN O
of IN O
. . O
South NNP B-geo
, , O
few JJ O
leader NN O
result NN O
and CC O
Gaza NNP B-geo
, , O
Happy JJ O
will MD O
situations NNS O
S&P NNP B-org
example NN O
in IN O
Secretary NNP B-per
today NN B-tim
a DT O
confiscate VB O
ire NN O
In IN O
Israeli JJ B-gpe
Woe NN O
new JJ O
into IN O
The DT O
89 CD B-tim
China NNP B-gpe
Barack NNP B-per
hopes NNS O
to TO O
Council NNP I-org
opponents NNS O
beyond IN O
The DT O
's POS O
, , O
. . O
main JJ O
and CC O
at IN O
carrying VBG O
the DT B-geo
on IN O
up RP O
, , O
professionals NNS O
the DT O
Ali NNP B-per
Thailand NNP I-geo
may MD O
vessel NN O
responsibility NN O
. . O
the DT O
by IN O
not RB O
unarmed JJ O
80 CD O
deaths NNS O
until IN O
to TO O
and CC O
. . O
. . O
. . O
by IN O
Shangla NNP B-geo
soldiers NNS O
other JJ O
was VBD O
a DT O
the DT O
has VBZ O
in IN O
amortizing JJ O
1848 CD B-tim
riots NNS O
the DT O
debate NN O
. . O
independence NN O
restart VB O
, , O
security NN O
military NN O
bird NN O
say VBP O
SELASSIE NNP I-per
of IN O
in IN O
officer NN O
that IN O
the DT O
Ehud NNP B-per
Kurds NNS O
's POS O
And CC O
other JJ O
more JJR O
( LRB O
business NN O
rose VBD O
now RB O
rule NN O
International NNP B-org
section NN O
, , O
, , O
storm NN O
, , O
and CC O
support VB O
intelligence NN O
which WDT O
Mr. NNP B-per
to TO O
part NN O
likely JJ O
attacked VBN O
to TO O
people NNS O
. . O
countries NNS O
Kurdish NNP O
's VBZ O
effect NN O
" `` O
as IN O
. . O
fell VBD O
Rafik NNP B-per
two CD O
citizens NNS O
end VB O
. . O
Tanzania NNP B-geo
has VBZ O
's POS O
" `` O
, , O
Minister NNP O
. . O
to TO O
( LRB O
nations NNS O
Japan NNP B-geo
new JJ O
of IN O
hours NNS O
of IN O
but CC O
islands NNS O
by IN O
, , O
his PRP$ O
Kozulin NNP I-per
to TO O
virus NN O
Sergei NNP B-per
presidential JJ O
Senior JJ O
Iraqi JJ B-gpe
of IN O
decision NN O
. . O
States NNP I-geo
against IN O
a DT O
petroleum NN O
Bertie NNP B-per
stage NN O
populations NNS O
later RB O
had VBN O
by IN O
has VBZ O
, , O
are VBP O
A.U. NNP I-art
unnamed JJ O
President NNP B-per
. . O
The DT O
year NN O
streetcar NN O
the DT O
for IN O
suicide NN O
Mr. NNP B-per
conviction NN O
to TO O
birds NNS O
fighting VBG O
130 CD O
a DT O
, , O
. . O
Dodge NNP B-art
controversial JJ O
French JJ B-gpe
. . O
daily JJ O
Katrina NNP I-tim
and CC O
A DT O
expected VBN O
Pakistan NNP B-geo
aid NN O
a DT O
Chad NNP B-geo
of IN O
as IN O
committing VBG O
The DT O
value NN O
write VB O
been VBN O
his PRP$ O
earlier RBR O
independence NN O
newspaper NN O
Allawi NNP I-per
Area NNP I-org
above IN O
by IN O
help VB O
survey NN O
rations NNS O
to TO O
had VBD O
Gates NNP I-per
down RP O
emission NN O
slightly RB O
a DT O
of IN O
the DT O
Defense NNP I-org
The DT O
of IN O
. . O
member NN O
female JJ O
from IN O
China NNP I-geo
for IN O
Merkel NNP I-per
Tehran NNP B-geo
. . O
however RB O
weakened VBN O
Group NNP I-org
Pacific NNP B-geo
, , O
In IN O
Gerais NNP I-geo
special JJ O
too RB O
crime NN O
of IN O
position NN O
, , O
pirates NNS O
other JJ O
Sunday NNP B-tim
shootout NN O
and CC O
in IN O
, , O
port JJ O
Sunday NNP B-tim
recovered VBN O
toppled VBD O
of IN I-org
or CC O
the DT O
continue VB O
. . O
border NN O
at IN O
. . O
. . O
under IN O
until IN O
's POS O
aid NN O
that IN O
The DT O
suicide NN O
a DT O
residents NNS O
's POS O
Israel NNP B-geo
outsider NN O
Friday NNP B-tim
helped VBD O
infection NN O
said VBD O
rejected VBD O
's POS O
simple JJ O
Israel NNP B-geo
Petraeus NNP B-per
million CD O
and CC O
economic JJ O
finally RB O
in IN O
, , O
the DT O
continues VBZ O
least JJS O
63 CD O
as IN O
last JJ O
decades NNS I-tim
so RB O
a DT O
Pakistan NNP B-geo
in IN O
to TO O
a DT O
century NN I-tim
IMF NNP B-org
workers NNS O
Scientists NNS O
assassination NN O
domestic JJ O
but CC O
to TO O
Species NNP I-art
Pakistan NNP B-geo
would MD O
up RP O
. . O
China NNP B-geo
first JJ O
shot VBN O
also RB O
heroin NN O
discussing VBG O
the DT O
General NNP B-per
and CC O
to TO O
's POS O
shirt NN O
rights NNS O
is VBZ O
that IN I-tim
with IN O
global JJ O
to TO O
Chad NNP I-geo
a DT O
to TO O
produce VB O
and CC O
from IN O
police NN O
sides NNS O
. . O
country NN O
plans NNS O
country NN O
draw VB O
U.S.-led JJ O
. . O
, , O
country NN O
torch NN O
AFP NNP B-org
and CC O
parliamentary JJ O
one CD O
